<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><record_update table="sys_metadata_link">
    <sys_metadata_link action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE">
        <directory>unload</directory>
        <documentkey>9887b9fcdb211010280df36f2996192e</documentkey>
        <payload><![CDATA[<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><record_update sys_domain="09ff3d105f231000b12e3572f2b4775d" table="x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1">
    <x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1 action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE">
        <active>true</active>
        <activity_due/>
        <additional_assignee_list/>
        <approval>not requested</approval>
        <approval_history/>
        <approval_set/>
        <ars_id display_value="ARS 3.1">43903e93dbcd1010280df36f299619aa</ars_id>
        <assessment_methods_and_objects>Examine: Access control policy; system</assessment_methods_and_objects>
        <assessment_objective>Determine if the organization has implemented all elements of this control as described in the control statements and implementation standard(s).</assessment_objective>
        <assigned_to/>
        <assignment_group/>
        <assurance/>
        <baseline>High; Moderate; Low</baseline>
        <business_duration/>
        <business_service/>
        <calendar_duration/>
        <close_notes/>
        <closed_at/>
        <closed_by/>
        <cmdb_ci/>
        <comments/>
        <comments_and_work_notes/>
        <company/>
        <contact_type/>
        <contract/>
        <control_definition>The organization monitors for unauthorized remote access to the information system (including access to internal networks by VPN). Remote access for privileged functions must be permitted only for compelling operational needs, must be strictly controlled, and must be explicitly authorized, in writing, by the CIO or his/her designated representative. If remote access is authorized, the organization: a. Establishes and documents usage restrictions, configuration/connection requirements, and implementation guidance for each type of remote access allowed; and b. Authorizes remote access to the information system prior to allowing such connections. c. Access to HHS Webmail using personally owned equipment is authorized. Access to other systems/networks using personally-owned equipment is prohibited without written authorization from the CIO, or an approved policy allowing the use of personally-owned equipment: 1. Personally-owned equipment must be scanned before being connected to CMS (and HHS) systems or networks to ensure compliance with CMS requirements; and 2. Personally-owned equipment must be prohibited from processing, accessing, or storing Department sensitive information unless it is approved in writing by the CMS SOP and employs CMS required encryption (FIPS 140-2 validated module).</control_definition>
        <control_family display_value="Access Control">408779fcdb211010280df36f29961977</control_family>
        <control_name>Remote Access</control_name>
        <control_number>AC-17</control_number>
        <control_type>Mandatory</control_type>
        <correlation_display/>
        <correlation_id/>
        <delivery_plan/>
        <delivery_task/>
        <description/>
        <due_date/>
        <escalation>0</escalation>
        <expected_start/>
        <follow_up/>
        <group_id>AC-17</group_id>
        <group_list/>
        <high>true</high>
        <impact>3</impact>
        <implementation_standards>High, Moderate &amp; Low:&#13;
&#13;
Std.1 - Require callback capability with re-authentication to verify connections from authorized locations when the Medicare Data Communications Network (MDCN) or Multi-Protoc</implementation_standards>
        <knowledge>false</knowledge>
        <location/>
        <low>true</low>
        <made_sla>true</made_sla>
        <moderate>true</moderate>
        <number>ARSC0010837</number>
        <opened_at>2020-06-19 13:21:21</opened_at>
        <opened_by display_value="System Administrator">6816f79cc0a8016401c5a33be04be441</opened_by>
        <order/>
        <parent/>
        <priority>3</priority>
        <reassignment_count>0</reassignment_count>
        <reference_policy>FedRAMP Rev. 4 Baseline; FISCAM: AC-1, AS-2; HIPAA: 45 C.F.R. ยง164.310(b), 45 C.F.R. ยง164.310(c); 45 C.F.R. ยง164.312(a)(1); 45 C.F.R. ยง164.312(e)(1); NIST SP: 800-46, 800-77, 800-113, 800-114, 800-121; OMB Memo: M-06-16, M-17-12</reference_policy>
        <rejection_goto/>
        <related_controls>AC-2, AC-3, AC-18, AC-19, AC-20, CA-3, C</related_controls>
        <service_offering/>
        <short_description/>
        <sla_due/>
        <standard>NIST-800</standard>
        <state>1</state>
        <supplemental_guidance>Remote access is access to organizational information systems by users (or processes acting on behalf of users) communicating through external networks (e.g., the Internet). Remote access methods include, for example, dial-up, broadband, and wireless. Organizations often employ encrypted VPNs to enhance confidentiality and integrity over remote connections. The use of encrypted VPNs, does not make the access non-remote; however, the use of VPNs, when adequately provisioned with appropriate security controls (e.g., employing appropriate encryption techniques for confidentiality and integrity protection) may provide sufficient assurance to the organization that it can effectively treat such connections as internal networks. Still, VPN connections traverse external networks, and the encrypted VPN does not enhance the availability of remote connections. Also, VPNs with encrypted tunnels can affect the organizational capability to adequately monitor network communications traffic for malicious code. Remote access controls apply to information systems other than public web servers or systems designed for public access. This control addresses authorization prior to allowing remote access without specifying the formats for such authorization. While organizations may use interconnection security agreements to authorize remote access connections, such agreements are not required by this control. Enforcing access restrictions for remote connections is addressed in AC-3.For minimum authentication requirements, refer to RMH, Volume III, Standard 3.1, CMS Authentication Standards.&#13;
&#13;
Guidance for systems processing, storing, or transmitting PII (to include PHI):&#13;
&#13;
Limiting access to personally identifiable information (PII) from remote networks and/or restricting activities that can be conducted with PII remotely reduces the risk of intentional and unintentional disclosures of PII that may not exist on an internal network.Allow remote access to PII only with two-factor authentication where one of the factors is provided by a device separate from the computer gaining access.&#13;
&#13;
Guidance for systems processing, storing, or transmitting PHI:&#13;
&#13;
Implement technical security measures to guard against unauthorized remote access to electronic PHI that is being transmitted over an electronic communications network.</supplemental_guidance>
        <sys_class_name>x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1</sys_class_name>
        <sys_created_by>admin</sys_created_by>
        <sys_created_on>2020-06-19 13:21:21</sys_created_on>
        <sys_domain>09ff3d105f231000b12e3572f2b4775d</sys_domain>
        <sys_domain_path>!!!/!!!/</sys_domain_path>
        <sys_id>9887b9fcdb211010280df36f2996192e</sys_id>
        <sys_mod_count>0</sys_mod_count>
        <sys_updated_by>admin</sys_updated_by>
        <sys_updated_on>2020-06-19 13:21:21</sys_updated_on>
        <task_for/>
        <time_worked/>
        <upon_approval>proceed</upon_approval>
        <upon_reject>cancel</upon_reject>
        <urgency>3</urgency>
        <user_input/>
        <variables/>
        <watch_list/>
        <wf_activity/>
        <work_end/>
        <work_notes/>
        <work_notes_list/>
        <work_start/>
    </x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1>
</record_update>
]]></payload>
        <sys_class_name>sys_metadata_link</sys_class_name>
        <sys_created_by>admin</sys_created_by>
        <sys_created_on>2020-06-23 20:26:22</sys_created_on>
        <sys_id>b42fbb06db251010280df36f2996196a</sys_id>
        <sys_mod_count>0</sys_mod_count>
        <sys_name>AC-17</sys_name>
        <sys_package display_value="Rapid ATO" source="x_415531_rapid_ato">64898e36db501010280df36f29961934</sys_package>
        <sys_policy/>
        <sys_scope display_value="Rapid ATO">64898e36db501010280df36f29961934</sys_scope>
        <sys_update_name>sys_metadata_link_b42fbb06db251010280df36f2996196a</sys_update_name>
        <sys_updated_by>admin</sys_updated_by>
        <sys_updated_on>2020-06-23 20:26:22</sys_updated_on>
        <tablename>x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1</tablename>
    </sys_metadata_link>
</record_update>
