<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><record_update table="sys_metadata_link">
    <sys_metadata_link action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE">
        <directory>unload</directory>
        <documentkey>f887b9fcdb211010280df36f2996199e</documentkey>
        <payload><![CDATA[<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><record_update sys_domain="09ff3d105f231000b12e3572f2b4775d" table="x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1">
    <x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1 action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE">
        <active>true</active>
        <activity_due/>
        <additional_assignee_list/>
        <approval>not requested</approval>
        <approval_history/>
        <approval_set/>
        <ars_id display_value="ARS 3.1">43903e93dbcd1010280df36f299619aa</ars_id>
        <assessment_methods_and_objects>Examine: Security assessment policy; p</assessment_methods_and_objects>
        <assessment_objective>Determine if the organization has implemented all elements of this control as described in the control statements and implementation standard(s).</assessment_objective>
        <assigned_to/>
        <assignment_group/>
        <assurance>Assurance</assurance>
        <baseline>High; Moderate; Low</baseline>
        <business_duration/>
        <business_service/>
        <calendar_duration/>
        <close_notes/>
        <closed_at/>
        <closed_by/>
        <cmdb_ci/>
        <comments/>
        <comments_and_work_notes/>
        <company/>
        <contact_type/>
        <contract/>
        <control_definition>The organization: a. Develops an information security and privacy control assessment plan that describes the scope of the assessment including:  1. Security and privacy controls and control enhancements under assessment (including information security and privacy changes enacted by HHS and CMS CIO/CISO directives); 2. Assessment procedures to be used to determine control effectiveness; and  3. Assessment environment, assessment team, and assessment roles and responsibilities. b. Assesses the security and privacy controls in the information system and its environment of operation, as defined in implementation standards, within every three hundred sixty-five (365) days in accordance with the CMS Information Security (IS) Acceptable Risk Safeguards (ARS) Including CMS Minimum Security Requirements (CMSR) Standard to determine the extent to which the controls are implemented correctly, operating as intended, and producing the desired outcome with respect to meeting established security and privacy requirements; c. Produces an assessment report that documents the results of the assessment; and d. Provides the results of the security and privacy control assessment within thirty (30) days after its completion, in writing, to the Business Owner responsible for the system and personnel responsible for reviewing the assessment documentation, and updating system security documentation where necessary to reflect any changes to the system.</control_definition>
        <control_family display_value="Security Assessment and Authorization">a887b9fcdb211010280df36f2996199b</control_family>
        <control_name>Security Assessments</control_name>
        <control_number>CA-02</control_number>
        <control_type>Mandatory</control_type>
        <correlation_display/>
        <correlation_id/>
        <delivery_plan/>
        <delivery_task/>
        <description/>
        <due_date/>
        <escalation>0</escalation>
        <expected_start/>
        <follow_up/>
        <group_id>CA-02</group_id>
        <group_list/>
        <high>true</high>
        <impact>3</impact>
        <implementation_standards>High, Moderate &amp; Low:&#13;
&#13;
Std.1 - An assessment of all controls must be conducted prior to issuing the initial authority to operate for all newly implemented systems. Std.2 - The annual assessment requ</implementation_standards>
        <knowledge>false</knowledge>
        <location/>
        <low>true</low>
        <made_sla>true</made_sla>
        <moderate>true</moderate>
        <number>ARSC0010894</number>
        <opened_at>2020-06-19 13:21:23</opened_at>
        <opened_by display_value="System Administrator">6816f79cc0a8016401c5a33be04be441</opened_by>
        <order/>
        <parent/>
        <priority>2</priority>
        <reassignment_count>0</reassignment_count>
        <reference_policy>Code: 5 United States Code (U.S.C.) §552a(b); Executive Order: 13587; FedRAMP Rev. 4 Baseline; Federal Information Processing Standard (FIPS) Pub: 199; FISCAM: AS-1, SM-5; HIPAA: 45 C.F.R. §164.308(a)(8); HSPD 7: D(11), F(19); NIST SP: 800-37, 800-39, 800-115, 800-137; OMB Memo: M-17-12 Att. 1, A.2.c, M-14-03, M-15-01, M-16-04</reference_policy>
        <rejection_goto/>
        <related_controls>AR-2, CA-5, CA-6, CA-7, PM-9, RA-5, SA-1</related_controls>
        <service_offering/>
        <short_description/>
        <sla_due/>
        <standard>NIST-800</standard>
        <state>1</state>
        <supplemental_guidance>Organizations assess security controls in organizational information system and the environments in which those systems operate as part of: (i) initial and ongoing security authorizations; (ii) FISMA annual assessments; (iii) continuous monitoring; and (iv) system development life cycle activities. Security assessments: (i) ensure that information security is built into organizational information systems; (ii) identify weaknesses and deficiencies early in the development process; (iii) provide essential information needed to make risk-based decisions as part of security authorization processes; and (iv) ensure compliance to vulnerability mitigation procedures. Assessments are conducted on the implemented security controls from NIST SP 800-53 Appendix F (main catalog) and NIST SP 800-53 Appendix G (Program Management controls) as documented in System Security Plans and Information Security Program Plans. Organizations can use other types of assessment activities such as vulnerability scanning and system monitoring to maintain the security posture of information systems during the entire life cycle. Security assessment reports document assessment results in sufficient detail as deemed necessary by CMS, to determine the accuracy and completeness of the reports and whether the security controls are implemented correctly, operating as intended, and producing the desired outcome with respect to meeting security requirements. The Federal Information Security Modernization Act (FISMA) requirement for assessing security controls at least annually does not require additional assessment activities to those activities already in place in organizational security authorization processes. Security assessment results are provided to the individuals or roles appropriate for the types of assessments being conducted. For example, assessments conducted in support of security authorization decisions are provided to authorizing officials or authorizing official designated representatives.To satisfy annual assessment requirements, organizations can use assessment results from the following sources, including but not limited to: (i) initial or ongoing information system authorizations; (ii) continuous monitoring; or (iii) system development life cycle activities. Organizations ensure that security assessment results are current, relevant to the determination of security control effectiveness; and obtained with the appropriate level of assessor independence. Existing security control assessment results can be reused to the extent that the results are still valid and can also be supplemented with additional assessments as needed.After initial authorizations and in accordance with OMB policy, organizations assess security controls during continuous monitoring. Organizations establish the security control selection criteria and subsequently selects a subset of the security controls within the information system and its environment of operation for assessment. Those security controls that are the most volatile (i.e., controls most affected by ongoing changes to the information system or its environment of operation) or deemed critical to protecting CMS operations and assets, individuals, other organizations, and the Nation are assessed more frequently in accordance with an organizational assessment of risk. All other controls are assessed at least once during the information system’s three-year authorization cycle. The organization can use the current year’s assessment results from any of the above sources to meet the FISMA annual assessment requirement if the results are current, valid, and relevant to determining security control effectiveness. Vulnerability Alerts provide useful examples of vulnerability mitigation procedures. External audits (e.g., audits by external entities such as regulatory agencies) are outside the scope of this control.&#13;
&#13;
Guidance for systems processing, storing, or transmitting PII (to include PHI):&#13;
&#13;
This control addresses the process of planning for and executing security assessments, the scope of which should include assessment of applicable privacy requirements.Once the final security assessment is completed, update the associated Privacy Impact Assessment (PIA) to reflect the results of the security assessment.</supplemental_guidance>
        <sys_class_name>x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1</sys_class_name>
        <sys_created_by>admin</sys_created_by>
        <sys_created_on>2020-06-19 13:21:23</sys_created_on>
        <sys_domain>09ff3d105f231000b12e3572f2b4775d</sys_domain>
        <sys_domain_path>!!!/!!!/</sys_domain_path>
        <sys_id>f887b9fcdb211010280df36f2996199e</sys_id>
        <sys_mod_count>0</sys_mod_count>
        <sys_updated_by>admin</sys_updated_by>
        <sys_updated_on>2020-06-19 13:21:23</sys_updated_on>
        <task_for/>
        <time_worked/>
        <upon_approval>proceed</upon_approval>
        <upon_reject>cancel</upon_reject>
        <urgency>3</urgency>
        <user_input/>
        <variables/>
        <watch_list/>
        <wf_activity/>
        <work_end/>
        <work_notes/>
        <work_notes_list/>
        <work_start/>
    </x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1>
</record_update>
]]></payload>
        <sys_class_name>sys_metadata_link</sys_class_name>
        <sys_created_by>admin</sys_created_by>
        <sys_created_on>2020-06-23 20:26:42</sys_created_on>
        <sys_id>c63f3346db251010280df36f29961902</sys_id>
        <sys_mod_count>0</sys_mod_count>
        <sys_name>CA-02</sys_name>
        <sys_package display_value="Rapid ATO" source="x_415531_rapid_ato">64898e36db501010280df36f29961934</sys_package>
        <sys_policy/>
        <sys_scope display_value="Rapid ATO">64898e36db501010280df36f29961934</sys_scope>
        <sys_update_name>sys_metadata_link_c63f3346db251010280df36f29961902</sys_update_name>
        <sys_updated_by>admin</sys_updated_by>
        <sys_updated_on>2020-06-23 20:26:42</sys_updated_on>
        <tablename>x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1</tablename>
    </sys_metadata_link>
</record_update>
