<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><record_update table="sys_metadata_link">
    <sys_metadata_link action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE">
        <directory>unload</directory>
        <documentkey>1487b9fcdb211010280df36f29961920</documentkey>
        <payload><![CDATA[<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><record_update sys_domain="09ff3d105f231000b12e3572f2b4775d" table="x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1">
    <x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1 action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE">
        <active>true</active>
        <activity_due/>
        <additional_assignee_list/>
        <approval>not requested</approval>
        <approval_history/>
        <approval_set/>
        <ars_id display_value="ARS 3.1">43903e93dbcd1010280df36f299619aa</ars_id>
        <assessment_methods_and_objects>Assessment 1Examine: Access control po</assessment_methods_and_objects>
        <assessment_objective>Determine if the organization has implemented all elements of this control as described in the control statements and implementation standard(s).&#13;
&#13;
Systems defined as CSPs:&#13;
&#13;
Determine if the organization has implemented all elements of this control as </assessment_objective>
        <assigned_to/>
        <assignment_group/>
        <assurance/>
        <baseline>High; Moderate; Low</baseline>
        <business_duration/>
        <business_service/>
        <calendar_duration/>
        <close_notes/>
        <closed_at/>
        <closed_by/>
        <cmdb_ci/>
        <comments/>
        <comments_and_work_notes/>
        <company/>
        <contact_type/>
        <contract/>
        <control_definition>The information system: a. Displays an approved system use notification message or banner before granting access to the system that provides privacy and security notices consistent with applicable federal laws, Executive Orders, directives, policies, regulations, standards, and guidance. The approved banner states:   * This warning banner provides privacy and security notices consistent with applicable federal laws, directives, and other federal guidance for accessing this Government system, which includes (1) this computer network, (2) all computers connected to this network, and (3) all devices and storage media attached to this network or to a computer on this network.  * This system is provided for Government authorized use only.  * Unauthorized or improper use of this system is prohibited and may result in disciplinary action and/or civil and criminal penalties.  * Personal use of social media and networking sites on this system is limited as to not interfere with official work duties and is subject to monitoring.  * By using this system, you understand and consent to the following:     - The Government may monitor, record, and audit your system usage, including usage of personal devices and email systems for official duties or to conduct HHS business. Therefore, you have no reasonable expectation of privacy regarding any communication or data transiting or stored on this system. At any time, and for any lawful Government purpose, the government may monitor, intercept, and search and seize any communication or data transiting or stored on this system.     - Any communication or data transiting or stored on this system may be disclosed or used for any lawful Government purposeb. Retains the notification message or banner on the screen until users take explicit actions to log on to or further access the information system; and c. For publicly accessible systems:   1. Displays system use information when appropriate, before granting further access;   2. Displays references, if any, to monitoring, recording, or auditing that are consistent with privacy accommodations for such systems that generally prohibit those activities; and   3. Includes a description of the authorized uses of the system.</control_definition>
        <control_family display_value="Access Control">408779fcdb211010280df36f29961977</control_family>
        <control_name>System Use Notification</control_name>
        <control_number>AC-08</control_number>
        <control_type>Mandatory</control_type>
        <correlation_display/>
        <correlation_id/>
        <delivery_plan/>
        <delivery_task/>
        <description/>
        <due_date/>
        <escalation>0</escalation>
        <expected_start/>
        <follow_up/>
        <group_id>AC-08</group_id>
        <group_list/>
        <high>true</high>
        <impact>3</impact>
        <implementation_standards>Systems defined as CSPs:&#13;
&#13;
High, Moderate &amp; Low:&#13;
&#13;
CSP.1 - For CSPs, the organization determines elements of the cloud environment that require the System Use Notification control. The elements of t</implementation_standards>
        <knowledge>false</knowledge>
        <location/>
        <low>true</low>
        <made_sla>true</made_sla>
        <moderate>true</moderate>
        <number>ARSC0010827</number>
        <opened_at>2020-06-19 13:21:21</opened_at>
        <opened_by display_value="System Administrator">6816f79cc0a8016401c5a33be04be441</opened_by>
        <order/>
        <parent/>
        <priority>3</priority>
        <reassignment_count>0</reassignment_count>
        <reference_policy>Code: 5 U.S.C. §552a(e)(3) and (e)(4); FedRAMP Rev. 4 Baseline; FISCAM: AC-1, AS-2; Department of Health and Human Services (HHS): Policy for Monitoring Employee Use of HHS IT Resources; OMB Circular A-130: 7.g.; 45 C.F.R. §164.520(1)(i)</reference_policy>
        <rejection_goto/>
        <related_controls>TR-1, TR-2</related_controls>
        <service_offering/>
        <short_description/>
        <sla_due/>
        <standard>NIST-800</standard>
        <state>1</state>
        <supplemental_guidance>The warning banner language has very important legal implications for CMS and its information system resources. Should content need to be added to this banner, submit the modified warning banner language to the CMS CIO for review and approval prior to implementation. If an information system has character limitations related to the warning banner display, the CMS CIO can provide an abbreviated warning banner version. If this banner is inconsistent with any directives, policies, regulations, or standards, notify the CMS CIO immediately.All information system computers and network devices under CMS control, prominently display the notice and consent banner immediately upon users’ authentication to the system, including, but not limited to, websites, web pages where substantial personal information from the public is collected, Secure File Transfer Protocol (SFTP), Secure Shell (SSH), or other services accessed.System use notifications can be implemented using messages or warning banners displayed before individuals log in to information systems. System use notifications are used only for access via logon interfaces with human users and are not required when such human interfaces do not exist.&#13;
&#13;
Guidance for systems processing, storing, or transmitting PII (to include PHI):&#13;
&#13;
System use notification (e.g., logon banner) does not satisfy the requirement for Privacy Act Statements or Privacy Act system of records notice, when applicable; see TR-1 and TR-2. System use notifications are the primary, interactive vehicle for notifying system users prior to accessing a system of the organization’s monitoring practices and reminding users that unauthorized use is both prohibited and subject to criminal and civil penalties. The system use notification requires explicit action from the system user to acknowledge the notice before they can enter the system. Notices on system use are principally intended to convey information regarding consent to monitor (and other security-relevant information). These notices may also be, in some instances, an appropriate means to remind system users that the system being accessed contains sensitive PII and requires due care (e.g., a logon banner on an employee management system).&#13;
&#13;
Guidance for systems processing, storing, or transmitting PHI:&#13;
&#13;
Note that System Use Notification does not satisfy the requirement for privacy notice under the HIPAA Privacy Rule.</supplemental_guidance>
        <sys_class_name>x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1</sys_class_name>
        <sys_created_by>admin</sys_created_by>
        <sys_created_on>2020-06-19 13:21:21</sys_created_on>
        <sys_domain>09ff3d105f231000b12e3572f2b4775d</sys_domain>
        <sys_domain_path>!!!/!!!/</sys_domain_path>
        <sys_id>1487b9fcdb211010280df36f29961920</sys_id>
        <sys_mod_count>0</sys_mod_count>
        <sys_updated_by>admin</sys_updated_by>
        <sys_updated_on>2020-06-19 13:21:21</sys_updated_on>
        <task_for/>
        <time_worked/>
        <upon_approval>proceed</upon_approval>
        <upon_reject>cancel</upon_reject>
        <urgency>3</urgency>
        <user_input/>
        <variables/>
        <watch_list/>
        <wf_activity/>
        <work_end/>
        <work_notes/>
        <work_notes_list/>
        <work_start/>
    </x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1>
</record_update>
]]></payload>
        <sys_class_name>sys_metadata_link</sys_class_name>
        <sys_created_by>admin</sys_created_by>
        <sys_created_on>2020-06-23 20:26:03</sys_created_on>
        <sys_id>1c1f3b06db251010280df36f2996191a</sys_id>
        <sys_mod_count>0</sys_mod_count>
        <sys_name>AC-08</sys_name>
        <sys_package display_value="Rapid ATO" source="x_415531_rapid_ato">64898e36db501010280df36f29961934</sys_package>
        <sys_policy/>
        <sys_scope display_value="Rapid ATO">64898e36db501010280df36f29961934</sys_scope>
        <sys_update_name>sys_metadata_link_1c1f3b06db251010280df36f2996191a</sys_update_name>
        <sys_updated_by>admin</sys_updated_by>
        <sys_updated_on>2020-06-23 20:26:03</sys_updated_on>
        <tablename>x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1</tablename>
    </sys_metadata_link>
</record_update>
