<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><record_update table="sys_metadata_link">
    <sys_metadata_link action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE">
        <directory>unload</directory>
        <documentkey>9f87bdfcdb211010280df36f29961943</documentkey>
        <payload><![CDATA[<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><record_update sys_domain="09ff3d105f231000b12e3572f2b4775d" table="x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1">
    <x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1 action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE">
        <active>true</active>
        <activity_due/>
        <additional_assignee_list/>
        <approval>not requested</approval>
        <approval_history/>
        <approval_set/>
        <ars_id display_value="ARS 3.1">43903e93dbcd1010280df36f299619aa</ars_id>
        <assessment_methods_and_objects>Systems processing, storing, or transm</assessment_methods_and_objects>
        <assessment_objective>Systems processing, storing, or transmitting PII (to include PHI):&#13;
&#13;
Determine if:(i) The organization provides means, where feasible and appropriate, for individuals to authorize the collection, use, maintaining, and sharing of PII prior to its collecti</assessment_objective>
        <assigned_to/>
        <assignment_group/>
        <assurance/>
        <baseline>High; Moderate; Low</baseline>
        <business_duration/>
        <business_service/>
        <calendar_duration/>
        <close_notes/>
        <closed_at/>
        <closed_by/>
        <cmdb_ci/>
        <comments/>
        <comments_and_work_notes/>
        <company/>
        <contact_type/>
        <contract/>
        <control_definition>Systems processing, storing, or transmitting PII (to include PHI):&#13;
&#13;
The organization: a. Provides means, where feasible and appropriate, for individuals to authorize the collection, use, maintaining, and sharing of PII prior to its collection; b. Provides appropriate means for individuals to understand the consequences of decisions to approve or decline the authorization of the collection, use, dissemination, and retention of PII; c. Obtains consent, where feasible and appropriate, from individuals prior to any new uses or disclosure of previously collected PII; and d. Ensures that individuals are aware of and, where feasible, consent to all uses of PII not initially described in the public notice that was in effect at the time the organization collected the PII.</control_definition>
        <control_family display_value="Individual Participation and Redress">9787bdfcdb211010280df36f29961942</control_family>
        <control_name>Consent</control_name>
        <control_number>IP-01</control_number>
        <control_type>Mandatory</control_type>
        <correlation_display/>
        <correlation_id/>
        <delivery_plan/>
        <delivery_task/>
        <description/>
        <due_date/>
        <escalation>0</escalation>
        <expected_start/>
        <follow_up/>
        <group_id>IP-01</group_id>
        <group_list/>
        <high>true</high>
        <impact>3</impact>
        <implementation_standards/>
        <knowledge>false</knowledge>
        <location/>
        <low>true</low>
        <made_sla>true</made_sla>
        <moderate>true</moderate>
        <number>ARSC0011267</number>
        <opened_at>2020-06-19 13:21:33</opened_at>
        <opened_by display_value="System Administrator">6816f79cc0a8016401c5a33be04be441</opened_by>
        <order/>
        <parent/>
        <priority>3</priority>
        <reassignment_count>0</reassignment_count>
        <reference_policy>CFR: 45 C.F.R. §164.506(b), 45 C.F.R. §164.508, 45 C.F.R. §164.510, 45 C.F.R. §164.522; Code: 5 U.S.C. §552a(e)(3)-(4); E-Gov: §208(c); OMB Memo: M-03-22, M-10-22; Privacy Act: §552a(b), §552a(e)(3)</reference_policy>
        <rejection_goto/>
        <related_controls>2, AP-1, TR-1, TR-2</related_controls>
        <service_offering/>
        <short_description/>
        <sla_due/>
        <standard>NIST-800</standard>
        <state>1</state>
        <supplemental_guidance>Guidance for systems processing, storing, or transmitting PII (to include PHI):&#13;
&#13;
Individual participation and agreement to provide information is fundamental to an individual making an informed decision regarding the collection, use, and safeguarding of their PII.Consent is fundamental to the participation of individuals in the decision-making process regarding the collection and use of their PII and the use of technologies that may increase risk to personal privacy. To obtain consent, organizations provide individuals appropriate notice of the purposes of the PII collection or technology use and a means for individuals to consent to the activity. Organizations tailor the public notice and consent mechanisms to meet operational needs. Organizations achieve awareness and consent, for example, through updated public notices.Organizations may obtain consent through opt-in, opt-out, or implied consent. Opt-in consent is the preferred method, but it is not always feasible. Opt-in requires that individuals take affirmative action to allow organizations to collect or use PII. For example, opt-in consent may require an individual to click a radio button on a website, or sign a document providing consent. In contrast, opt-out requires individuals to act to prevent the new or continued collection or use of such PII. For example, the Federal Trade Commission’s Do-Not-Call Registry allows individuals to opt-out of receiving unsolicited telemarketing calls by requesting to be added to a list. Implied consent is the least preferred method and should be used only in limited circumstances. Implied consent occurs where individuals’ behavior or failure to object indicates agreement with the collection or use of PII (e.g., by entering and remaining in a building where notice has been posted that security cameras are in use, the individual implies consent to the video recording). Depending upon the nature of the program or information system, it may be appropriate to allow individuals to limit the types of PII they provide and subsequent uses of that PII. Organizational consent mechanisms include a discussion of the consequences to individuals of failure to provide PII. Consequences can vary from organization to organization.Whenever feasible, opt-in is the preferred method to obtain consent.&#13;
&#13;
Guidance for systems processing, storing, or transmitting PHI:&#13;
&#13;
Consent is a term under HIPAA with specific meaning not equivalent to a HIPAA authorization.  For example, see: Uses and disclosures to carry out treatment, payment, or health care operations (45 C.F.R. §164.506); Uses and Disclosures for Which an Authorization is Required (45 C.F.R. §164.508); Uses and Disclosures Requiring an Opportunity to Agree/Object (45 C.F.R. §164.510); Right to Request Privacy Protection for Protected Health Information (45 C.F.R. §164.522).</supplemental_guidance>
        <sys_class_name>x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1</sys_class_name>
        <sys_created_by>admin</sys_created_by>
        <sys_created_on>2020-06-19 13:21:33</sys_created_on>
        <sys_domain>09ff3d105f231000b12e3572f2b4775d</sys_domain>
        <sys_domain_path>!!!/!!!/</sys_domain_path>
        <sys_id>9f87bdfcdb211010280df36f29961943</sys_id>
        <sys_mod_count>0</sys_mod_count>
        <sys_updated_by>admin</sys_updated_by>
        <sys_updated_on>2020-06-19 13:21:33</sys_updated_on>
        <task_for/>
        <time_worked/>
        <upon_approval>proceed</upon_approval>
        <upon_reject>cancel</upon_reject>
        <urgency>3</urgency>
        <user_input/>
        <variables/>
        <watch_list/>
        <wf_activity/>
        <work_end/>
        <work_notes/>
        <work_notes_list/>
        <work_start/>
    </x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1>
</record_update>
]]></payload>
        <sys_class_name>sys_metadata_link</sys_class_name>
        <sys_created_by>admin</sys_created_by>
        <sys_created_on>2020-06-23 20:26:23</sys_created_on>
        <sys_id>912fbb06db251010280df36f2996198c</sys_id>
        <sys_mod_count>0</sys_mod_count>
        <sys_name>IP-01</sys_name>
        <sys_package display_value="Rapid ATO" source="x_415531_rapid_ato">64898e36db501010280df36f29961934</sys_package>
        <sys_policy/>
        <sys_scope display_value="Rapid ATO">64898e36db501010280df36f29961934</sys_scope>
        <sys_update_name>sys_metadata_link_912fbb06db251010280df36f2996198c</sys_update_name>
        <sys_updated_by>admin</sys_updated_by>
        <sys_updated_on>2020-06-23 20:26:23</sys_updated_on>
        <tablename>x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1</tablename>
    </sys_metadata_link>
</record_update>
