<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><record_update table="sys_metadata_link">
    <sys_metadata_link action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE">
        <directory>unload</directory>
        <documentkey>e6873dfcdb211010280df36f299619df</documentkey>
        <payload><![CDATA[<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><record_update sys_domain="09ff3d105f231000b12e3572f2b4775d" table="x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1">
    <x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1 action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE">
        <active>true</active>
        <activity_due/>
        <additional_assignee_list/>
        <approval>not requested</approval>
        <approval_history/>
        <approval_set/>
        <ars_id display_value="ARS 3.1">43903e93dbcd1010280df36f299619aa</ars_id>
        <assessment_methods_and_objects>Examine: System and communications pro</assessment_methods_and_objects>
        <assessment_objective>Determine if the organization has implemented all elements of this control as described in the control statements and implementation standard(s).&#13;
&#13;
Systems defined as CSPs:&#13;
&#13;
Determine if the organization has implemented all elements of this control as </assessment_objective>
        <assigned_to/>
        <assignment_group/>
        <assurance/>
        <baseline>High; Moderate</baseline>
        <business_duration/>
        <business_service/>
        <calendar_duration/>
        <close_notes/>
        <closed_at/>
        <closed_by/>
        <cmdb_ci/>
        <comments/>
        <comments_and_work_notes/>
        <company/>
        <contact_type/>
        <contract/>
        <control_definition>The information system protects the confidentiality and integrity of information at rest, as defined in the HHS Standard for Encryption of Computing Devices and Information.&#13;
&#13;
Systems processing, storing, or transmitting PII (to include PHI):&#13;
&#13;
The information system protects the confidentiality and integrity of personally identifiable information (PII).&#13;
&#13;
Systems defined as CSPs:&#13;
&#13;
For CSPs, the information system enforces encryption of the instance (container) image files under the hypervisor:  - Instance (container) image files from virtual server and client deployments must be encrypted in a manner that meets FIPS 140-2 validated requirements.</control_definition>
        <control_family display_value="System and Communications Protection">9e873dfcdb211010280df36f29961960</control_family>
        <control_name>Protection of Information at Rest</control_name>
        <control_number>SC-28</control_number>
        <control_type>Mandatory</control_type>
        <correlation_display/>
        <correlation_id/>
        <delivery_plan/>
        <delivery_task/>
        <description/>
        <due_date/>
        <escalation>0</escalation>
        <expected_start/>
        <follow_up/>
        <group_id>SC-28</group_id>
        <group_list/>
        <high>true</high>
        <impact>3</impact>
        <implementation_standards>Systems defined as CSPs:&#13;
&#13;
High &amp; Moderate:&#13;
&#13;
CSP.1 - CSPs support the capability to use cryptographic mechanisms to protect information at rest.</implementation_standards>
        <knowledge>false</knowledge>
        <location/>
        <low>false</low>
        <made_sla>true</made_sla>
        <moderate>true</moderate>
        <number>ARSC0011184</number>
        <opened_at>2020-06-19 13:21:31</opened_at>
        <opened_by display_value="System Administrator">6816f79cc0a8016401c5a33be04be441</opened_by>
        <order/>
        <parent/>
        <priority>3</priority>
        <reassignment_count>0</reassignment_count>
        <reference_policy>FedRAMP Rev. 4 Baseline; NIST SP: 800-56, 800-57, 800-111; 5 U.S.C. §552a(b) and (e)(10); OMB Memo: M-06-16, M-17-12 Att. 1, C.; 45 C.F.R. §164.312(a)(2)(iv); 45 C.F.R.§164.312(e)(2)(ii)</reference_policy>
        <rejection_goto/>
        <related_controls>AC-3, AC-6, CA-7, CM-3, CM-5, CM-6, PE-3</related_controls>
        <service_offering/>
        <short_description/>
        <sla_due/>
        <standard>NIST-800</standard>
        <state>1</state>
        <supplemental_guidance>This control addresses the confidentiality and integrity of information at rest and covers user information and system information. Information at rest refers to the state of information when it is located on storage devices as specific components of information systems. System-related information requiring protection includes, for example, configurations or rule sets for firewalls, gateways, intrusion detection/prevention systems, filtering routers, and authenticator content. Organizations may employ different mechanisms to achieve confidentiality and integrity protections, including the use of cryptographic mechanisms and file share scanning. Integrity protection can be achieved, for example, by implementing Write-Once-Read-Many (WORM) technologies. Organizations may also employ other security controls including, for example, secure off-line storage in lieu of online storage when adequate protection of information at rest cannot otherwise be achieved and/or continuous monitoring to identify malicious code at rest.&#13;
&#13;
Guidance for systems processing, storing, or transmitting PII (to include PHI):&#13;
&#13;
Because of the sensitivity of PII and protected health information (PHI), the confidentiality and integrity of such information must be assured for data at rest.&#13;
&#13;
Guidance for systems processing, storing, or transmitting PHI:&#13;
&#13;
Under the HIPAA Security Rule, this is an addressable implementation specification. HIPAA covered entities must conduct an analysis as described at 45 C.F.R. § 164.306 (Security standards: General rules) part (d) (Implementation specifications) to determine how it must be applied within the organization. However, using cryptographic protection allows the organization to utilize the “Safe Harbor” provision under the Breach Notification Rule.  If PHI is encrypted pursuant to the Guidance Specifying the Technologies and Methodologies that Render Protected Health Information Unusable, Unreadable, or Indecipherable to Unauthorized Individuals (74 FR 42740), then no breach notification is required following an impermissible use or disclosure of the information.  Therefore, organizations should use cryptographic protections for PHI stored on electronic media.</supplemental_guidance>
        <sys_class_name>x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1</sys_class_name>
        <sys_created_by>admin</sys_created_by>
        <sys_created_on>2020-06-19 13:21:31</sys_created_on>
        <sys_domain>09ff3d105f231000b12e3572f2b4775d</sys_domain>
        <sys_domain_path>!!!/!!!/</sys_domain_path>
        <sys_id>e6873dfcdb211010280df36f299619df</sys_id>
        <sys_mod_count>0</sys_mod_count>
        <sys_updated_by>admin</sys_updated_by>
        <sys_updated_on>2020-06-19 13:21:31</sys_updated_on>
        <task_for/>
        <time_worked/>
        <upon_approval>proceed</upon_approval>
        <upon_reject>cancel</upon_reject>
        <urgency>3</urgency>
        <user_input/>
        <variables/>
        <watch_list/>
        <wf_activity/>
        <work_end/>
        <work_notes/>
        <work_notes_list/>
        <work_start/>
    </x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1>
</record_update>
]]></payload>
        <sys_class_name>sys_metadata_link</sys_class_name>
        <sys_created_by>admin</sys_created_by>
        <sys_created_on>2020-06-23 20:26:39</sys_created_on>
        <sys_id>953fbf06db251010280df36f299619be</sys_id>
        <sys_mod_count>0</sys_mod_count>
        <sys_name>SC-28</sys_name>
        <sys_package display_value="Rapid ATO" source="x_415531_rapid_ato">64898e36db501010280df36f29961934</sys_package>
        <sys_policy/>
        <sys_scope display_value="Rapid ATO">64898e36db501010280df36f29961934</sys_scope>
        <sys_update_name>sys_metadata_link_953fbf06db251010280df36f299619be</sys_update_name>
        <sys_updated_by>admin</sys_updated_by>
        <sys_updated_on>2020-06-23 20:26:39</sys_updated_on>
        <tablename>x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1</tablename>
    </sys_metadata_link>
</record_update>
