<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><record_update table="sys_metadata_link">
    <sys_metadata_link action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE">
        <directory>unload</directory>
        <documentkey>d987f9fcdb211010280df36f2996194e</documentkey>
        <payload><![CDATA[<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><record_update sys_domain="09ff3d105f231000b12e3572f2b4775d" table="x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1">
    <x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1 action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE">
        <active>true</active>
        <activity_due/>
        <additional_assignee_list/>
        <approval>not requested</approval>
        <approval_history/>
        <approval_set/>
        <ars_id display_value="ARS 3.1">43903e93dbcd1010280df36f299619aa</ars_id>
        <assessment_methods_and_objects>Examine: Identification and authentica</assessment_methods_and_objects>
        <assessment_objective>Determine if the organization has implemented all elements of this control as described in the control statements and implementation standard(s).</assessment_objective>
        <assigned_to/>
        <assignment_group/>
        <assurance/>
        <baseline>High; Moderate; Low</baseline>
        <business_duration/>
        <business_service/>
        <calendar_duration/>
        <close_notes/>
        <closed_at/>
        <closed_by/>
        <cmdb_ci/>
        <comments/>
        <comments_and_work_notes/>
        <company/>
        <contact_type/>
        <contract/>
        <control_definition>The organization manages information system identifiers by: a. Receiving authorization from defined personnel or roles (defined in the applicable security plan) to assign an individual, group, role, or device identifier; b. Selecting an identifier that identifies an individual, group, role, or device; c. Assigning the identifier to the intended individual, group, role, or device; d. Preventing reuse of identifiers until all previous access authorizations are removed from the system, including all file accesses for that identifier but not before a period of three (3) years or more has passed; and e. Disabling the identifier after the following periods of in activity: 30 days for High, 60 days for Moderate, or 90 days for Low systems.&#13;
&#13;
Systems processing, storing, or transmitting PII (to include PHI):&#13;
&#13;
Social security numbers (SSNs), and parts of SSNs, must not be used as system identifiers. Identifier management must ensure that any access to, or action involving, personally identifiable information (PII) is attributable to a unique individual.</control_definition>
        <control_family display_value="Identification and Authentication">9587f9fcdb211010280df36f2996193a</control_family>
        <control_name>Identifier Management</control_name>
        <control_number>IA-04</control_number>
        <control_type>Mandatory</control_type>
        <correlation_display/>
        <correlation_id/>
        <delivery_plan/>
        <delivery_task/>
        <description/>
        <due_date/>
        <escalation>0</escalation>
        <expected_start/>
        <follow_up/>
        <group_id>IA-04</group_id>
        <group_list/>
        <high>true</high>
        <impact>3</impact>
        <implementation_standards>Systems defined as CSPs:&#13;
&#13;
High, Moderate &amp; Low:&#13;
&#13;
CSP.1 - For CSPs, the organization prevents reuse of user or device identifiers for at least two (2) years and disables the user identifier after n</implementation_standards>
        <knowledge>false</knowledge>
        <location/>
        <low>true</low>
        <made_sla>true</made_sla>
        <moderate>true</moderate>
        <number>ARSC0010995</number>
        <opened_at>2020-06-19 13:21:25</opened_at>
        <opened_by display_value="System Administrator">6816f79cc0a8016401c5a33be04be441</opened_by>
        <order/>
        <parent/>
        <priority>3</priority>
        <reassignment_count>0</reassignment_count>
        <reference_policy>FedRAMP Rev. 4 Baseline; FISCAM: AC-2, AS-2; HIPAA: 45 C.F.R. §164.312(a)(2)(i), 45 C.F.R. §164.312(d); 45 C.F.R. §164.308(a)(4); 45 C.F.R. §164.308(a)(5)(ii)(D)</reference_policy>
        <rejection_goto/>
        <related_controls>AC-2, IA-2, IA-3, IA-5, IA-8, SC-37</related_controls>
        <service_offering/>
        <short_description/>
        <sla_due/>
        <standard>NIST-800</standard>
        <state>1</state>
        <supplemental_guidance>Common device identifiers include, for example, media access control (MAC), Internet protocol (IP) addresses, or device-unique token identifiers. Management of individual identifiers is not applicable to shared information system accounts (e.g., guest and anonymous accounts). Typically, individual identifiers are the user names of the information system accounts assigned to those individuals. In such instances, the account management activities of AC-2 use account names provided by IA-4. This control also addresses individual identifiers not necessarily associated with information system accounts (e.g., identifiers used in physical security control databases accessed by badge reader systems for access to information systems). Preventing reuse of identifiers implies preventing the assignment of previously used individual, group, role, or device identifiers to different individuals, groups, roles, or devices.&#13;
&#13;
Guidance for systems processing, storing, or transmitting PII (to include PHI):&#13;
&#13;
Identifiers are a critical and necessary function to confirm which people and devices are accessing sensitive information such as PII. Using SSNs as identifiers may create the potential for unauthorized disclosure of the SSN and linkage of that individual to other PII, as system identifiers are not protected with the same level of security as are database elements or passwords. In addition, collecting an individual’s SSN may create notice requirements under the Privacy Act.&#13;
&#13;
Guidance for systems processing, storing, or transmitting PHI:&#13;
&#13;
Identifier management must ensure that any access to, or action involving, PHI is attributable to a unique individual.</supplemental_guidance>
        <sys_class_name>x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1</sys_class_name>
        <sys_created_by>admin</sys_created_by>
        <sys_created_on>2020-06-19 13:21:25</sys_created_on>
        <sys_domain>09ff3d105f231000b12e3572f2b4775d</sys_domain>
        <sys_domain_path>!!!/!!!/</sys_domain_path>
        <sys_id>d987f9fcdb211010280df36f2996194e</sys_id>
        <sys_mod_count>0</sys_mod_count>
        <sys_updated_by>admin</sys_updated_by>
        <sys_updated_on>2020-06-19 13:21:25</sys_updated_on>
        <task_for/>
        <time_worked/>
        <upon_approval>proceed</upon_approval>
        <upon_reject>cancel</upon_reject>
        <urgency>3</urgency>
        <user_input/>
        <variables/>
        <watch_list/>
        <wf_activity/>
        <work_end/>
        <work_notes/>
        <work_notes_list/>
        <work_start/>
    </x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1>
</record_update>
]]></payload>
        <sys_class_name>sys_metadata_link</sys_class_name>
        <sys_created_by>admin</sys_created_by>
        <sys_created_on>2020-06-23 20:26:36</sys_created_on>
        <sys_id>5c3f7f06db251010280df36f2996198b</sys_id>
        <sys_mod_count>0</sys_mod_count>
        <sys_name>IA-04</sys_name>
        <sys_package display_value="Rapid ATO" source="x_415531_rapid_ato">64898e36db501010280df36f29961934</sys_package>
        <sys_policy/>
        <sys_scope display_value="Rapid ATO">64898e36db501010280df36f29961934</sys_scope>
        <sys_update_name>sys_metadata_link_5c3f7f06db251010280df36f2996198b</sys_update_name>
        <sys_updated_by>admin</sys_updated_by>
        <sys_updated_on>2020-06-23 20:26:36</sys_updated_on>
        <tablename>x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1</tablename>
    </sys_metadata_link>
</record_update>
