<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><record_update table="sys_metadata_link">
    <sys_metadata_link action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE">
        <directory>unload</directory>
        <documentkey>76877dfcdb211010280df36f2996191b</documentkey>
        <payload><![CDATA[<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><record_update sys_domain="09ff3d105f231000b12e3572f2b4775d" table="x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1">
    <x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1 action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE">
        <active>true</active>
        <activity_due/>
        <additional_assignee_list/>
        <approval>not requested</approval>
        <approval_history/>
        <approval_set/>
        <ars_id display_value="ARS 3.1">43903e93dbcd1010280df36f299619aa</ars_id>
        <assessment_methods_and_objects>Examine: System and information integr</assessment_methods_and_objects>
        <assessment_objective>Determine if the organization has implemented all elements of this control as described in the control statements and implementation standard(s).</assessment_objective>
        <assigned_to/>
        <assignment_group/>
        <assurance>Assurance</assurance>
        <baseline>High; Moderate; Low</baseline>
        <business_duration/>
        <business_service/>
        <calendar_duration/>
        <close_notes/>
        <closed_at/>
        <closed_by/>
        <cmdb_ci/>
        <comments/>
        <comments_and_work_notes/>
        <company/>
        <contact_type/>
        <contract/>
        <control_definition>The organization: a. Monitors the information system to detect:   1. Attacks and indicators of potential attacks in accordance with the current RMH, Chapter 08: Incident Response; and   2. Unauthorized local, network, and remote connections as defined by (twice High and Moderate or once for Low) weekly; b. Identifies unauthorized use of the information system through defined techniques and methods (defined in the applicable System Security Plan); c. Deploys monitoring devices:   1. Strategically within the information system to collect organization-determined essential information; and   2. At ad hoc locations within the system to track specific types of transactions of interest to the organization. d. Protects information obtained from intrusion-monitoring tools from unauthorized access, modification, and deletion; e. Heightens the level of information system monitoring activity whenever there is an indication of increased risk to organizational operations and assets, individuals, other organizations, or the Nation based on law enforcement information, intelligence information, or other credible sources of information; f. Obtains legal opinion about information system monitoring activities in accordance with applicable federal laws, Executive Orders, directives, policies, or regulations; and g. Provides defined information system monitoring information (defined in the applicable System Security Plan) to defined personnel or roles (defined in the applicable System Security Plan) as needed, and at defined frequency (defined in the applicable System Security Plan).</control_definition>
        <control_family display_value="System and Information Integrity">aa873dfcdb211010280df36f299619f4</control_family>
        <control_name>Information System Monitoring</control_name>
        <control_number>SI-04</control_number>
        <control_type>Mandatory</control_type>
        <correlation_display/>
        <correlation_id/>
        <delivery_plan/>
        <delivery_task/>
        <description/>
        <due_date/>
        <escalation>0</escalation>
        <expected_start/>
        <follow_up/>
        <group_id>SI-04</group_id>
        <group_list/>
        <high>true</high>
        <impact>3</impact>
        <implementation_standards>High, Moderate &amp; Low:&#13;
&#13;
Std.1 - Implement a centrally managed Intrusion detection system/intrusion protection system (IDS/IPS) capability to monitor network communications on all networks and subnets</implementation_standards>
        <knowledge>false</knowledge>
        <location/>
        <low>true</low>
        <made_sla>true</made_sla>
        <moderate>true</moderate>
        <number>ARSC0011198</number>
        <opened_at>2020-06-19 13:21:31</opened_at>
        <opened_by display_value="System Administrator">6816f79cc0a8016401c5a33be04be441</opened_by>
        <order/>
        <parent/>
        <priority>3</priority>
        <reassignment_count>0</reassignment_count>
        <reference_policy>Code: 5 U.S.C. §552a(b), (e)(10); FedRAMP Rev. 4 Baseline; FISCAM: AC-5, AS-2; HIPAA: 45 C.F.R. §164.308(a)(1)(ii)(D), 45 C.F.R. §164.308(a)(5)(ii)(B), 45 C.F.R. §164.308(a)(6)(ii); NIST SP: 800-61, 800-83, 800-92, 800-94, 800-137; OMB Memo: M-17-12, M-14-03, M-15-01, M-16-04; OMB Circular A-130: 7.g.</reference_policy>
        <rejection_goto/>
        <related_controls>AC-3, AC-4, AC-8, AC-17, AU-2, AU-6, AU-</related_controls>
        <service_offering/>
        <short_description/>
        <sla_due/>
        <standard>NIST-800</standard>
        <state>1</state>
        <supplemental_guidance>Information system monitoring includes external and internal monitoring. External monitoring includes the observation of events occurring at the information system boundary (i.e., part of perimeter defense and boundary protection). Internal monitoring includes the observation of events occurring within the information system. Organizations can monitor information systems, for example, by observing audit activities in real-time or by observing other system aspects such as access patterns, characteristics of access, and other actions. The monitoring objectives may guide determination of the events. Information system monitoring capability is achieved through a variety of tools and techniques (e.g., intrusion detection systems, intrusion prevention systems, malicious code protection software, scanning tools, audit record monitoring software, network monitoring software). Strategic locations for monitoring devices include, for example, selected perimeter locations and near server farms supporting critical applications, with such devices typically being employed at the managed interfaces associated with controls SC-7 and AC-17. Einstein network monitoring devices from DHS can also be included as monitoring devices. The granularity of monitoring information collected is based on organizational monitoring objectives and the capability of information systems to support such objectives. Specific types of transactions of interest include, for example, HTTP traffic that bypasses HTTP proxies. Information system monitoring is an integral part of organizational continuous monitoring and incident response programs. Output from system monitoring serves as input to continuous monitoring and incident response programs. A network connection is any connection with a device that communicates through a network (e.g., local area network, Internet). A remote connection is any connection with a device communicating through an external network (e.g., the Internet). Local, network, and remote connections can be either wired or wireless.&#13;
&#13;
Guidance for systems processing, storing, or transmitting PII (to include PHI):&#13;
&#13;
Intrusion-monitoring tools may collect personally identifiable information (PII) of all types. Notice to users who are monitored should be provided prior to system use. Controls sufficient to protect the type of PII collected must be in place for the technology performing the monitoring, including encryption of monitoring data that may contain PII. When conducting information system monitoring on internal or external networks which may collect PII, the organization should coordinate with the organization’s counsel and privacy officer.</supplemental_guidance>
        <sys_class_name>x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1</sys_class_name>
        <sys_created_by>admin</sys_created_by>
        <sys_created_on>2020-06-19 13:21:31</sys_created_on>
        <sys_domain>09ff3d105f231000b12e3572f2b4775d</sys_domain>
        <sys_domain_path>!!!/!!!/</sys_domain_path>
        <sys_id>76877dfcdb211010280df36f2996191b</sys_id>
        <sys_mod_count>0</sys_mod_count>
        <sys_updated_by>admin</sys_updated_by>
        <sys_updated_on>2020-06-19 13:21:31</sys_updated_on>
        <task_for/>
        <time_worked/>
        <upon_approval>proceed</upon_approval>
        <upon_reject>cancel</upon_reject>
        <urgency>3</urgency>
        <user_input/>
        <variables/>
        <watch_list/>
        <wf_activity/>
        <work_end/>
        <work_notes/>
        <work_notes_list/>
        <work_start/>
    </x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1>
</record_update>
]]></payload>
        <sys_class_name>sys_metadata_link</sys_class_name>
        <sys_created_by>admin</sys_created_by>
        <sys_created_on>2020-06-23 20:26:16</sys_created_on>
        <sys_id>eb1f7b06db251010280df36f299619c6</sys_id>
        <sys_mod_count>0</sys_mod_count>
        <sys_name>SI-04</sys_name>
        <sys_package display_value="Rapid ATO" source="x_415531_rapid_ato">64898e36db501010280df36f29961934</sys_package>
        <sys_policy/>
        <sys_scope display_value="Rapid ATO">64898e36db501010280df36f29961934</sys_scope>
        <sys_update_name>sys_metadata_link_eb1f7b06db251010280df36f299619c6</sys_update_name>
        <sys_updated_by>admin</sys_updated_by>
        <sys_updated_on>2020-06-23 20:26:16</sys_updated_on>
        <tablename>x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1</tablename>
    </sys_metadata_link>
</record_update>
