<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><record_update table="sys_metadata_link">
    <sys_metadata_link action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE">
        <directory>unload</directory>
        <documentkey>8c87b9fcdb211010280df36f29961911</documentkey>
        <payload><![CDATA[<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><record_update sys_domain="09ff3d105f231000b12e3572f2b4775d" table="x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1">
    <x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1 action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE">
        <active>true</active>
        <activity_due/>
        <additional_assignee_list/>
        <approval>not requested</approval>
        <approval_history/>
        <approval_set/>
        <ars_id display_value="ARS 3.1">43903e93dbcd1010280df36f299619aa</ars_id>
        <assessment_methods_and_objects>Examine: Access control policy; system</assessment_methods_and_objects>
        <assessment_objective>Determine if the organization has implemented all elements of this control as described in the control statements and implementation standard(s).&#13;
&#13;
Systems defined as CSPs:&#13;
&#13;
Determine if the organization has implemented all elements of this control as </assessment_objective>
        <assigned_to/>
        <assignment_group/>
        <assurance/>
        <baseline>High; Moderate; Low</baseline>
        <business_duration/>
        <business_service/>
        <calendar_duration/>
        <close_notes/>
        <closed_at/>
        <closed_by/>
        <cmdb_ci/>
        <comments/>
        <comments_and_work_notes/>
        <company/>
        <contact_type/>
        <contract/>
        <control_definition>The organization: a. Separates duties of individuals as necessary (defined in the applicable security plan), to prevent malicious activity without collusion; b. Documents separation of duties; and c. Defines information system access authorizations to support separation of duties.&#13;
&#13;
Systems defined as CSPs:&#13;
&#13;
For CSPs, the information system enforces role-based access control policies over all subjects and objects where the policy specifies that: a. The policy is uniformly enforced across all subjects and objects within the boundary of the information system; andb. A subject that has been granted access to information is constrained from doing any of the following;  1. Passing the information to unauthorized subjects or objects;  2. Granting its privileges to other subjects;  3. Changing one or more security attributes on subjects, objects, the information system, or information system components;  4. Choosing the security attributes and attribute values to be associated with newly created or modified objects; or  5. Changing the rules governing access control.</control_definition>
        <control_family display_value="Access Control">408779fcdb211010280df36f29961977</control_family>
        <control_name>Separation of Duties</control_name>
        <control_number>AC-05</control_number>
        <control_type>Mandatory</control_type>
        <correlation_display/>
        <correlation_id/>
        <delivery_plan/>
        <delivery_task/>
        <description/>
        <due_date/>
        <escalation>0</escalation>
        <expected_start/>
        <follow_up/>
        <group_id>AC-05</group_id>
        <group_list/>
        <high>true</high>
        <impact>3</impact>
        <implementation_standards>High:&#13;
&#13;
Std.1 - Audit functions must not be performed by security personnel responsible for administering access control. Std.2 - Maintain a limited group of administrators with access based upon the</implementation_standards>
        <knowledge>false</knowledge>
        <location/>
        <low>true</low>
        <made_sla>true</made_sla>
        <moderate>true</moderate>
        <number>ARSC0010817</number>
        <opened_at>2020-06-19 13:21:21</opened_at>
        <opened_by display_value="System Administrator">6816f79cc0a8016401c5a33be04be441</opened_by>
        <order/>
        <parent/>
        <priority>3</priority>
        <reassignment_count>0</reassignment_count>
        <reference_policy>Code: 5 U.S.C. §552a(e)(9)-(e)(10); FedRAMP Rev. 4 Baseline; FISCAM: AS-4, SD-1, SD-2; HIPAA: 45 C.F.R. §164.308(a)(3)(i), 164.308(a)(4)(i), 45 C.F.R. §164.308(a)(4)(ii)(A), 45 C.F.R. §164.312(a)(1); 45 C.F.R. §164.312(c)(1)</reference_policy>
        <rejection_goto/>
        <related_controls>AC-3, AC-6, PE-3, PE-4, PS-2</related_controls>
        <service_offering/>
        <short_description/>
        <sla_due/>
        <standard>NIST-800</standard>
        <state>1</state>
        <supplemental_guidance>Separation of duties addresses the potential for abuse of authorized privileges and helps to reduce the risk of malevolent activity without collusion. Separation of duties includes, for example: (i) dividing mission functions and information system support functions among different individuals and/or roles; (ii) conducting information system support functions with different individuals (e.g., system management, programming, configuration management, quality assurance and testing, and network security); and (iii) ensuring security personnel administering access control functions do not also administer audit functions.Separation of duties aligns privileges with appropriate roles with the idea that duties are split between roles in such a way as to reduce the risk of malevolent or inappropriate behaviors based on access. Implementing this control helps reduce the risk of inappropriate access to sensitive information (e.g., separating employees that perform security investigations from mission and business functions).&#13;
&#13;
Guidance for systems processing, storing, or transmitting PII (to include PHI):&#13;
&#13;
Separation of duties aligns privileges with appropriate roles with the idea that duties are split between roles in such a way as to reduce the risk of malevolent or inappropriate behaviors based on access. Implementing this control helps reduce the risk of inappropriate access to PII (e.g., separating employees that perform security investigations from mission and business functions).Separation of duties is implemented by designating a selected set of administrators the capability to set user permissions to PII and PHI information, while those administrators do not themselves have access to the PII and PHI. The principle of separation of duties is significant for developers as well as for operational system administrators.&#13;
&#13;
Guidance for systems processing, storing, or transmitting PHI:&#13;
&#13;
HIPAA requires the separation of duties to ensure that checks and balances are designed into the system to limit the effect of any given end user to control the entire process. Roles and responsibilities should be divided so that a single end user cannot subvert a critical process. This practice divides the tasks related to maintaining system security among different personnel such that no single individual could compromise PHI.</supplemental_guidance>
        <sys_class_name>x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1</sys_class_name>
        <sys_created_by>admin</sys_created_by>
        <sys_created_on>2020-06-19 13:21:21</sys_created_on>
        <sys_domain>09ff3d105f231000b12e3572f2b4775d</sys_domain>
        <sys_domain_path>!!!/!!!/</sys_domain_path>
        <sys_id>8c87b9fcdb211010280df36f29961911</sys_id>
        <sys_mod_count>0</sys_mod_count>
        <sys_updated_by>admin</sys_updated_by>
        <sys_updated_on>2020-06-19 13:21:21</sys_updated_on>
        <task_for/>
        <time_worked/>
        <upon_approval>proceed</upon_approval>
        <upon_reject>cancel</upon_reject>
        <urgency>3</urgency>
        <user_input/>
        <variables/>
        <watch_list/>
        <wf_activity/>
        <work_end/>
        <work_notes/>
        <work_notes_list/>
        <work_start/>
    </x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1>
</record_update>
]]></payload>
        <sys_class_name>sys_metadata_link</sys_class_name>
        <sys_created_by>admin</sys_created_by>
        <sys_created_on>2020-06-23 20:26:19</sys_created_on>
        <sys_id>1c2fbb06db251010280df36f29961922</sys_id>
        <sys_mod_count>0</sys_mod_count>
        <sys_name>AC-05</sys_name>
        <sys_package display_value="Rapid ATO" source="x_415531_rapid_ato">64898e36db501010280df36f29961934</sys_package>
        <sys_policy/>
        <sys_scope display_value="Rapid ATO">64898e36db501010280df36f29961934</sys_scope>
        <sys_update_name>sys_metadata_link_1c2fbb06db251010280df36f29961922</sys_update_name>
        <sys_updated_by>admin</sys_updated_by>
        <sys_updated_on>2020-06-23 20:26:19</sys_updated_on>
        <tablename>x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1</tablename>
    </sys_metadata_link>
</record_update>
