<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><record_update table="sys_metadata_link">
    <sys_metadata_link action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE">
        <directory>unload</directory>
        <documentkey>0987b9fcdb211010280df36f299619fb</documentkey>
        <payload><![CDATA[<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><record_update sys_domain="09ff3d105f231000b12e3572f2b4775d" table="x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1">
    <x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1 action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE">
        <active>true</active>
        <activity_due/>
        <additional_assignee_list/>
        <approval>not requested</approval>
        <approval_history/>
        <approval_set/>
        <ars_id display_value="ARS 3.1">43903e93dbcd1010280df36f299619aa</ars_id>
        <assessment_methods_and_objects>Examine: Contingency planning policy; </assessment_methods_and_objects>
        <assessment_objective>Determine if the organization has implemented all elements of this control as described in the control statements and implementation standard(s).</assessment_objective>
        <assigned_to/>
        <assignment_group/>
        <assurance/>
        <baseline>High; Moderate; Low</baseline>
        <business_duration/>
        <business_service/>
        <calendar_duration/>
        <close_notes/>
        <closed_at/>
        <closed_by/>
        <cmdb_ci/>
        <comments/>
        <comments_and_work_notes/>
        <company/>
        <contact_type/>
        <contract/>
        <control_definition>The organization: a. Develops a contingency plan for the information system in accordance with NIST SP 800-34 that:    1. Identifies essential CMS missions and business functions and associated contingency requirements;    2. Provides recovery objectives, restoration priorities, and metrics;    3. Addresses contingency roles and responsibilities, and assigns these to specific individuals with contact information;    4. Addresses maintaining essential CMS missions and business functions despite an information system disruption, compromise, or failure;    5. Addresses eventual, full information system restoration without deterioration of the security safeguards originally planned and implemented; and    6. Is reviewed and approved by designated officials within the organization. b. Distributes copies of the contingency plan to the ISSO, Business Owner, Contingency Plan Coordinator (CPC), and other stakeholders identified within the contingency plan; c. Coordinates contingency planning activities with incident handling activities; d. Reviews the contingency plan for the information system within every three hundred sixty-five (365) days; e. Updates the contingency plan to address changes to the organization, information system, or environment of operation and problems encountered during contingency plan implementation, execution, or testing; f. Communicates contingency plan changes to key contingency personnel, system administrator, database administrator, and other personnel/roles as appropriate and organizational elements identified above; and g. Protects the contingency plan from unauthorized disclosure and modification.</control_definition>
        <control_family display_value="Contingency Planning">c587b9fcdb211010280df36f299619f8</control_family>
        <control_name>Contingency Plan</control_name>
        <control_number>CP-02</control_number>
        <control_type>Mandatory</control_type>
        <correlation_display/>
        <correlation_id/>
        <delivery_plan/>
        <delivery_task/>
        <description/>
        <due_date/>
        <escalation>0</escalation>
        <expected_start/>
        <follow_up/>
        <group_id>CP-02</group_id>
        <group_list/>
        <high>true</high>
        <impact>3</impact>
        <implementation_standards>High, Moderate &amp; Low:&#13;
&#13;
Std.1 - The system must be continuously monitored and assessed to ensure that it is operating as intended and that changes do not have an adverse effect on system performance.</implementation_standards>
        <knowledge>false</knowledge>
        <location/>
        <low>true</low>
        <made_sla>true</made_sla>
        <moderate>true</moderate>
        <number>ARSC0010947</number>
        <opened_at>2020-06-19 13:21:24</opened_at>
        <opened_by display_value="System Administrator">6816f79cc0a8016401c5a33be04be441</opened_by>
        <order/>
        <parent/>
        <priority>3</priority>
        <reassignment_count>0</reassignment_count>
        <reference_policy>FedRAMP Rev. 4 Baseline; FISCAM: AS-5, CP-3; HIPAA: 45 C.F.R. §164.308(a)(7)(ii)(B), 45 C.F.R. §164.308(a)(7)(ii)(C), 45 C.F.R. §164.308(a)(7)(ii)(E), 45 C.F.R. §164.308(a)(7)(i)-(ii); 45 C.F.R. §164.310(a)(2)(i); 45 C.F.R. §164.312(a)(2)(ii); Homeland Security Presidential Directive (HSPD) 7: G(22)(i); NIST SP: 800-34;</reference_policy>
        <rejection_goto/>
        <related_controls>AC-14, CP-6, CP-7, CP-8, CP-9, CP-10, IR</related_controls>
        <service_offering/>
        <short_description/>
        <sla_due/>
        <standard>NIST-800</standard>
        <state>1</state>
        <supplemental_guidance>Contingency planning for information systems is part of an overall organizational program for achieving continuity of operations for mission/business functions. Contingency planning addresses both information system restoration and implementation of alternative mission/business processes when systems are impacted.  The effectiveness of contingency planning is maximized by considering such planning throughout the phases of the system development life cycle. Performing contingency planning on hardware, software, and firmware development can be an effective means of achieving information system resiliency. Contingency plans reflect the degree of restoration required for organizational information systems since not all systems may need to fully recover to achieve the level of continuity of operations desired. Information system recovery objectives reflect applicable laws, Executive Orders, directives, policies, standards, regulations, and guidelines. In addition to information system availability, contingency plans also address other security-related events resulting in a reduction in mission and/or business effectiveness, such as malicious attacks compromising the confidentiality or integrity of information systems. Actions addressed in contingency plans include, for example, orderly/graceful degradation, information system shutdown, fallback to a manual mode, alternate information flows, and operating in modes reserved for when systems are under attack. By closely coordinating contingency planning with incident handling activities, organizations can ensure that the necessary contingency planning activities are in place and activated in the event of a security incident.&#13;
&#13;
Guidance for systems processing, storing, or transmitting PII (to include PHI):&#13;
&#13;
Contingency plans must take privacy-applicable requirements into account so that executing contingency measures does not result in avoidable privacy incidents and breaches.&#13;
&#13;
Guidance for systems processing, storing, or transmitting PHI:&#13;
&#13;
The contingency plan for systems containing PHI must include:  1)    Data backup plan,  2)    Disaster recovery plan,  3)    Emergency mode operation plan, and   4)    Emergency access procedures.Additionally, the decision to include the following is dependent on a risk analysis to determine if or to what extent these should be included in the contingency plan:  1)    Testing and revision procedures,  2)    Applications and data criticality analysis, and  3)    Contingency operations (i.e., procedures that allow facility access in support of restoration of lost data.</supplemental_guidance>
        <sys_class_name>x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1</sys_class_name>
        <sys_created_by>admin</sys_created_by>
        <sys_created_on>2020-06-19 13:21:24</sys_created_on>
        <sys_domain>09ff3d105f231000b12e3572f2b4775d</sys_domain>
        <sys_domain_path>!!!/!!!/</sys_domain_path>
        <sys_id>0987b9fcdb211010280df36f299619fb</sys_id>
        <sys_mod_count>0</sys_mod_count>
        <sys_updated_by>admin</sys_updated_by>
        <sys_updated_on>2020-06-19 13:21:24</sys_updated_on>
        <task_for/>
        <time_worked/>
        <upon_approval>proceed</upon_approval>
        <upon_reject>cancel</upon_reject>
        <urgency>3</urgency>
        <user_input/>
        <variables/>
        <watch_list/>
        <wf_activity/>
        <work_end/>
        <work_notes/>
        <work_notes_list/>
        <work_start/>
    </x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1>
</record_update>
]]></payload>
        <sys_class_name>sys_metadata_link</sys_class_name>
        <sys_created_by>admin</sys_created_by>
        <sys_created_on>2020-06-23 20:26:02</sys_created_on>
        <sys_id>c41ff706db251010280df36f299619ee</sys_id>
        <sys_mod_count>0</sys_mod_count>
        <sys_name>CP-02</sys_name>
        <sys_package display_value="Rapid ATO" source="x_415531_rapid_ato">64898e36db501010280df36f29961934</sys_package>
        <sys_policy/>
        <sys_scope display_value="Rapid ATO">64898e36db501010280df36f29961934</sys_scope>
        <sys_update_name>sys_metadata_link_c41ff706db251010280df36f299619ee</sys_update_name>
        <sys_updated_by>admin</sys_updated_by>
        <sys_updated_on>2020-06-23 20:26:02</sys_updated_on>
        <tablename>x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1</tablename>
    </sys_metadata_link>
</record_update>
