<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><record_update table="sys_metadata_link">
    <sys_metadata_link action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE">
        <directory>unload</directory>
        <documentkey>1a873dfcdb211010280df36f2996194f</documentkey>
        <payload><![CDATA[<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><record_update sys_domain="09ff3d105f231000b12e3572f2b4775d" table="x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1">
    <x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1 action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE">
        <active>true</active>
        <activity_due/>
        <additional_assignee_list/>
        <approval>not requested</approval>
        <approval_history/>
        <approval_set/>
        <ars_id display_value="ARS 3.1">43903e93dbcd1010280df36f299619aa</ars_id>
        <assessment_methods_and_objects>Examine: System and services acquisiti</assessment_methods_and_objects>
        <assessment_objective>Determine if the organization has implemented all elements of this control as described in the control statements and implementation standard(s).&#13;
&#13;
Systems processing, storing, or transmitting PII (to include PHI):&#13;
&#13;
Determine if the organization has im</assessment_objective>
        <assigned_to/>
        <assignment_group/>
        <assurance>Assurance</assurance>
        <baseline>High; Moderate</baseline>
        <business_duration/>
        <business_service/>
        <calendar_duration/>
        <close_notes/>
        <closed_at/>
        <closed_by/>
        <cmdb_ci/>
        <comments/>
        <comments_and_work_notes/>
        <company/>
        <contact_type/>
        <contract/>
        <control_definition>The organization requires the developer of the information system, system component, or information system service to:a. Create and implement a security assessment plan in accordance with, but not limited to, current CMS procedures;b. Perform unit; integration; system; and regression testing/evaluation in accordance with the CMS eXpedited Life Cycle (XLC);c. Produce evidence of the execution of the security assessment plan and the results of the security testing/evaluation;d. Implement a verifiable flaw remediation process; ande. Correct flaws identified during security testing/evaluation.&#13;
&#13;
Systems processing, storing, or transmitting PII (to include PHI):&#13;
&#13;
For information systems containing PII, the organization requires the developer of the information system, system component, or information system service to:  a. Create and implement a security assessment plan that includes assessment of privacy controls.  b. Conduct tests that:    1. Minimize to the use of PII to the maximum extent practicable;    2. Use actual PII only if a formal memorandum of agreement (MOA), memorandum of understanding (MOU), or data exchange agreement has been established between the data owner of the PII and the entity developing/testing the information system including how loss, theft, or compromise (i.e., breach) of PII is to be handled;     3. Use de-identified or anonymized PII to the maximum extent practicable; and    4. Coordinate use of PII with the privacy office before conducting any testing.</control_definition>
        <control_family display_value="System and Services Acquisition">9e873dfcdb211010280df36f29961936</control_family>
        <control_name>Developer Security Testing and Evaluation</control_name>
        <control_number>SA-11</control_number>
        <control_type>Mandatory</control_type>
        <correlation_display/>
        <correlation_id/>
        <delivery_plan/>
        <delivery_task/>
        <description/>
        <due_date/>
        <escalation>0</escalation>
        <expected_start/>
        <follow_up/>
        <group_id>SA-11</group_id>
        <group_list/>
        <high>true</high>
        <impact>3</impact>
        <implementation_standards>High &amp; Moderate:&#13;
&#13;
Std.1 - If the security control assessment results are used in support of the security authorization process for the information system, ensure that no security relevant modificati</implementation_standards>
        <knowledge>false</knowledge>
        <location/>
        <low>false</low>
        <made_sla>true</made_sla>
        <moderate>true</moderate>
        <number>ARSC0011137</number>
        <opened_at>2020-06-19 13:21:29</opened_at>
        <opened_by display_value="System Administrator">6816f79cc0a8016401c5a33be04be441</opened_by>
        <order/>
        <parent/>
        <priority>2</priority>
        <reassignment_count>0</reassignment_count>
        <reference_policy>Code: 5 U.S.C. ยง552a(e)(10); E-Government Act of 2002 (Pub. L. No. 107-347), ยง208, and Title III; FedRAMP Rev. 4 Baseline; FISCAM: AS-3, CM-3; ISO/IEC: 15408; OMB Memo: M-03-22; OMB Circular A-130: 7.g.; Web: capec.mitre.org, cve.mitre.org, cwe.mitre.org, nvd.nist.gov</reference_policy>
        <rejection_goto/>
        <related_controls>CA-2, CM-4, SA-3, SA-4, SA-5, SI-2, AR-7</related_controls>
        <service_offering/>
        <short_description/>
        <sla_due/>
        <standard>NIST-800</standard>
        <state>1</state>
        <supplemental_guidance>Developmental security testing/evaluation occurs at all post-design phases of the system development life cycle. Such testing/evaluation confirms that the required security controls are implemented correctly, operating as intended, enforcing the desired security policy, and meeting established security requirements. Security properties of information systems may be affected by the interconnection of system components or changes to those components. These interconnections or changes (e.g., upgrading or replacing applications and operating systems) may adversely affect previously implemented security controls. This control provides additional types of security testing/evaluation that developers can conduct to reduce or eliminate potential flaws. Testing custom software applications may require approaches such as static analysis, dynamic analysis, binary analysis, or a hybrid of the three approaches. Developers can employ these analysis approaches in a variety of tools (e.g., web-based application scanners, static analysis tools, binary analyzers) and in source code reviews. Security assessment plans provide the specific activities that developers plan to carry out including the types of analyses, testing, evaluation, and reviews of software and firmware components, the degree of rigor to be applied, and the types of artifacts produced during those processes. The depth of security testing/evaluation refers to the rigor and level of detail associated with the assessment process (e.g., black box, gray box, or white box testing). The coverage of security testing/evaluation refers to the scope (i.e., number and type) of the artifacts included in the assessment process. Contracts specify the acceptance criteria for security assessment plans, flaw remediation processes, and the evidence that the plans/processes have been diligently applied. Methods for reviewing and protecting assessment plans, evidence, and documentation are commensurate with the security category or classification level of the information system. Contracts may specify documentation protection requirements.&#13;
&#13;
Guidance for systems processing, storing, or transmitting PII (to include PHI):&#13;
&#13;
Testing is a key method to ensure privacy controls are implemented. Including privacy controls in the security assessment plan ensures they are tested.</supplemental_guidance>
        <sys_class_name>x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1</sys_class_name>
        <sys_created_by>admin</sys_created_by>
        <sys_created_on>2020-06-19 13:21:29</sys_created_on>
        <sys_domain>09ff3d105f231000b12e3572f2b4775d</sys_domain>
        <sys_domain_path>!!!/!!!/</sys_domain_path>
        <sys_id>1a873dfcdb211010280df36f2996194f</sys_id>
        <sys_mod_count>0</sys_mod_count>
        <sys_updated_by>admin</sys_updated_by>
        <sys_updated_on>2020-06-19 13:21:29</sys_updated_on>
        <task_for/>
        <time_worked/>
        <upon_approval>proceed</upon_approval>
        <upon_reject>cancel</upon_reject>
        <urgency>3</urgency>
        <user_input/>
        <variables/>
        <watch_list/>
        <wf_activity/>
        <work_end/>
        <work_notes/>
        <work_notes_list/>
        <work_start/>
    </x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1>
</record_update>
]]></payload>
        <sys_class_name>sys_metadata_link</sys_class_name>
        <sys_created_by>admin</sys_created_by>
        <sys_created_on>2020-06-23 20:26:04</sys_created_on>
        <sys_id>e41f3b06db251010280df36f2996192f</sys_id>
        <sys_mod_count>0</sys_mod_count>
        <sys_name>SA-11</sys_name>
        <sys_package display_value="Rapid ATO" source="x_415531_rapid_ato">64898e36db501010280df36f29961934</sys_package>
        <sys_policy/>
        <sys_scope display_value="Rapid ATO">64898e36db501010280df36f29961934</sys_scope>
        <sys_update_name>sys_metadata_link_e41f3b06db251010280df36f2996192f</sys_update_name>
        <sys_updated_by>admin</sys_updated_by>
        <sys_updated_on>2020-06-23 20:26:04</sys_updated_on>
        <tablename>x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1</tablename>
    </sys_metadata_link>
</record_update>
