<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><record_update table="sys_metadata_link">
    <sys_metadata_link action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE">
        <directory>unload</directory>
        <documentkey>5487b9fcdb211010280df36f2996192a</documentkey>
        <payload><![CDATA[<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><record_update sys_domain="09ff3d105f231000b12e3572f2b4775d" table="x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1">
    <x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1 action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE">
        <active>true</active>
        <activity_due/>
        <additional_assignee_list/>
        <approval>not requested</approval>
        <approval_history/>
        <approval_set/>
        <ars_id display_value="ARS 3.1">43903e93dbcd1010280df36f299619aa</ars_id>
        <assessment_methods_and_objects>Examine: Access control policy; proced</assessment_methods_and_objects>
        <assessment_objective>Determine if the organization has implemented all elements of this control as described in the control statements and implementation standard(s).</assessment_objective>
        <assigned_to/>
        <assignment_group/>
        <assurance/>
        <baseline>High; Moderate; Low</baseline>
        <business_duration/>
        <business_service/>
        <calendar_duration/>
        <close_notes/>
        <closed_at/>
        <closed_by/>
        <cmdb_ci/>
        <comments/>
        <comments_and_work_notes/>
        <company/>
        <contact_type/>
        <contract/>
        <control_definition>The organization: a. Identifies specific user actions that can be performed on the information system without identification or authentication; b. Documents and provides supporting rationale in the security plan for the information system, user actions not requiring identification or authentication; and c. Configures Information systems to permit public access only to the extent necessary to accomplish mission objectives, without first requiring individual identification and authentication.</control_definition>
        <control_family display_value="Access Control">408779fcdb211010280df36f29961977</control_family>
        <control_name>Permitted Actions Without Identification or Authentication</control_name>
        <control_number>AC-14</control_number>
        <control_type>Mandatory</control_type>
        <correlation_display/>
        <correlation_id/>
        <delivery_plan/>
        <delivery_task/>
        <description/>
        <due_date/>
        <escalation>0</escalation>
        <expected_start/>
        <follow_up/>
        <group_id>AC-14</group_id>
        <group_list/>
        <high>true</high>
        <impact>3</impact>
        <implementation_standards/>
        <knowledge>false</knowledge>
        <location/>
        <low>true</low>
        <made_sla>true</made_sla>
        <moderate>true</moderate>
        <number>ARSC0010834</number>
        <opened_at>2020-06-19 13:21:21</opened_at>
        <opened_by display_value="System Administrator">6816f79cc0a8016401c5a33be04be441</opened_by>
        <order/>
        <parent/>
        <priority>1</priority>
        <reassignment_count>0</reassignment_count>
        <reference_policy>Code: 5 U.S.C. ยง552a(b); FedRAMP Rev. 4 Baseline; FISCAM: AC-2, AS-2; OMB Circular A-130: 7.g. and Appendix III; 45 C.F.R. ยง164.312(a)(2)(i)</reference_policy>
        <rejection_goto/>
        <related_controls>AC-2(9), CP-2, IA-2</related_controls>
        <service_offering/>
        <short_description/>
        <sla_due/>
        <standard>NIST-800</standard>
        <state>1</state>
        <supplemental_guidance>This control addresses situations in which organizations determine that no identification or authentication is required in organizational information systems. Organizations may allow a limited number of user actions without identification or authentication, including, for example, when individuals access public websites or other publicly accessible federal information systems, when individuals use mobile phones to receive calls, or when facsimiles are received. Organizations also identify actions that normally require identification or authentication but may under certain circumstances (e.g., emergencies), allow identification or authentication mechanisms to be bypassed. Such bypasses may occur, for example, via a software-readable physical switch that commands bypass of the logon functionality and is protected from accidental or unmonitored use. This control does not apply to situations where identification and authentication have already occurred and are not repeated, but rather to situations where identification and authentication have not yet occurred. Organizations may decide that there are no user actions that can be performed on organizational information systems without identification and authentication and thus, the values for assignment statements can be none.&#13;
&#13;
Guidance for systems processing, storing, or transmitting PII (to include PHI):&#13;
&#13;
Individual accountability requires the ability to trace (audit) the actions of the user who initiated them when accessing personally identifiable information (PII). Therefore, un-identified and un-authenticated users must not access PII.&#13;
&#13;
Guidance for systems processing, storing, or transmitting PHI:&#13;
&#13;
Individual accountability requires the ability to trace (audit) the actions of the user who initiated them when accessing PHI.  Therefore, un- identified and un-authenticated users must not access PHI.</supplemental_guidance>
        <sys_class_name>x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1</sys_class_name>
        <sys_created_by>admin</sys_created_by>
        <sys_created_on>2020-06-19 13:21:21</sys_created_on>
        <sys_domain>09ff3d105f231000b12e3572f2b4775d</sys_domain>
        <sys_domain_path>!!!/!!!/</sys_domain_path>
        <sys_id>5487b9fcdb211010280df36f2996192a</sys_id>
        <sys_mod_count>0</sys_mod_count>
        <sys_updated_by>admin</sys_updated_by>
        <sys_updated_on>2020-06-19 13:21:21</sys_updated_on>
        <task_for/>
        <time_worked/>
        <upon_approval>proceed</upon_approval>
        <upon_reject>cancel</upon_reject>
        <urgency>3</urgency>
        <user_input/>
        <variables/>
        <watch_list/>
        <wf_activity/>
        <work_end/>
        <work_notes/>
        <work_notes_list/>
        <work_start/>
    </x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1>
</record_update>
]]></payload>
        <sys_class_name>sys_metadata_link</sys_class_name>
        <sys_created_by>admin</sys_created_by>
        <sys_created_on>2020-06-23 20:26:11</sys_created_on>
        <sys_id>5a1f7b06db251010280df36f2996192d</sys_id>
        <sys_mod_count>0</sys_mod_count>
        <sys_name>AC-14</sys_name>
        <sys_package display_value="Rapid ATO" source="x_415531_rapid_ato">64898e36db501010280df36f29961934</sys_package>
        <sys_policy/>
        <sys_scope display_value="Rapid ATO">64898e36db501010280df36f29961934</sys_scope>
        <sys_update_name>sys_metadata_link_5a1f7b06db251010280df36f2996192d</sys_update_name>
        <sys_updated_by>admin</sys_updated_by>
        <sys_updated_on>2020-06-23 20:26:11</sys_updated_on>
        <tablename>x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1</tablename>
    </sys_metadata_link>
</record_update>
