<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><record_update table="sys_metadata_link">
    <sys_metadata_link action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE">
        <directory>unload</directory>
        <documentkey>7587f9fcdb211010280df36f299619b7</documentkey>
        <payload><![CDATA[<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><record_update sys_domain="09ff3d105f231000b12e3572f2b4775d" table="x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1">
    <x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1 action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE">
        <active>true</active>
        <activity_due/>
        <additional_assignee_list/>
        <approval>not requested</approval>
        <approval_history/>
        <approval_set/>
        <ars_id display_value="ARS 3.1">43903e93dbcd1010280df36f299619aa</ars_id>
        <assessment_methods_and_objects>Examine: Information system media prot</assessment_methods_and_objects>
        <assessment_objective>Determine if the organization has implemented all elements of this control as described in the control statements and implementation standard(s).</assessment_objective>
        <assigned_to/>
        <assignment_group/>
        <assurance/>
        <baseline>High; Moderate</baseline>
        <business_duration/>
        <business_service/>
        <calendar_duration/>
        <close_notes/>
        <closed_at/>
        <closed_by/>
        <cmdb_ci/>
        <comments/>
        <comments_and_work_notes/>
        <company/>
        <contact_type/>
        <contract/>
        <control_definition>Commensurate with the FIPS 199 security categorizations for confidentiality and integrity of the data, the organization: a. Protects and controls digital and non-digital media defined within the latest revision of NIST SP 800-88, Guidelines for Media Sanitization, and HHS Information Systems Security and Privacy Policy (IS2P) Appendix I, containing sensitive information during transport outside of controlled areas using cryptography and tamper evident packaging, and:    1. if hand carried, using a securable container (e.g., locked briefcase) via authorized personnel, or    2. if shipped, trackable with receipt by commercial carrier. b. Maintains accountability for information system media during transport outside of controlled areas; c. Documents activities associated with the transport of information system media; and d. Restricts the activities associated with the transport of information system media to authorized personnel.&#13;
&#13;
Systems processing, storing, or transmitting PII (to include PHI):&#13;
&#13;
The organization protects and controls digital media that contains personally identifiable information (PII) during transport outside of controlled areas using FIPS-validated encryption.&#13;
&#13;
Systems processing, storing, or transmitting PHI:&#13;
&#13;
The organization protects and controls digital media that contains protected health information (PHI) during transport outside of controlled areas using a FIPS 140-2 validated cryptographic module operating in the FIPS-approved mode of operation.</control_definition>
        <control_family display_value="Media Protection">ed87f9fcdb211010280df36f299619af</control_family>
        <control_name>Media Transport</control_name>
        <control_number>MP-05</control_number>
        <control_type>Mandatory</control_type>
        <correlation_display/>
        <correlation_id/>
        <delivery_plan/>
        <delivery_task/>
        <description/>
        <due_date/>
        <escalation>0</escalation>
        <expected_start/>
        <follow_up/>
        <group_id>MP-05</group_id>
        <group_list/>
        <high>true</high>
        <impact>3</impact>
        <implementation_standards>Systems processing, storing, or transmitting PII (to include PHI):&#13;
&#13;
High &amp; Moderate:&#13;
&#13;
PRIV.1 - Protect and control non-digital PII/PHI media during transport outside of controlled areas and restri</implementation_standards>
        <knowledge>false</knowledge>
        <location/>
        <low>false</low>
        <made_sla>true</made_sla>
        <moderate>true</moderate>
        <number>ARSC0011055</number>
        <opened_at>2020-06-19 13:21:27</opened_at>
        <opened_by display_value="System Administrator">6816f79cc0a8016401c5a33be04be441</opened_by>
        <order/>
        <parent/>
        <priority>3</priority>
        <reassignment_count>0</reassignment_count>
        <reference_policy/>
        <rejection_goto/>
        <related_controls>AC-19, CP-9, MP-3, MP-4, RA-3, SC-8, SC-</related_controls>
        <service_offering/>
        <short_description/>
        <sla_due/>
        <standard>NIST-800</standard>
        <state>1</state>
        <supplemental_guidance>Information system media includes both digital and non-digital media. Digital media includes, for example, diskettes, magnetic tapes, external/removable hard disk drives, flash drives, compact disks, and digital video disks. Non-digital media includes, for example, paper and microfilm. This control also applies to mobile devices with information storage capability (e.g., smart phones, tablets, E-readers), that are transported outside of controlled areas. Controlled areas are areas or spaces for which organizations provide sufficient physical and/or procedural safeguards to meet the requirements established for protecting information and/or information systems.Physical and technical safeguards for media are commensurate with the security category or classification of the information residing on the media. Safeguards to protect media during transport include, for example, locked containers and cryptography. Cryptographic mechanisms can provide confidentiality and integrity protections depending upon the mechanisms used. Activities associated with transport include the actual transport as well as those activities such as releasing media for transport and ensuring that media enters the appropriate transport processes. For the actual transport, authorized transport and courier personnel may include individuals from outside the organization (e.g., U.S. Postal Service or a commercial transport or delivery service). Maintaining accountability of media during transport includes, for example, restricting transport activities to authorized personnel and tracking and/or obtaining explicit records of transport activities as the media moves through the transportation system to prevent and detect loss, destruction, or tampering. Organizations establish documentation requirements for activities associated with the transport of information system media in accordance with organizational assessments of risk to include the flexibility to define different record-keeping methods for the different types of media transport as part of an overall system of transport-related records.&#13;
&#13;
Guidance for systems processing, storing, or transmitting PII (to include PHI):&#13;
&#13;
Protecting and controlling media containing sensitive information, such as PII, commensurate with the sensitivity of the information contained on the media, during transport outside of controlled areas, promotes accountability and limits situations that make the media vulnerable to unauthorized use and disclosure through loss, theft, or other mishandling.</supplemental_guidance>
        <sys_class_name>x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1</sys_class_name>
        <sys_created_by>admin</sys_created_by>
        <sys_created_on>2020-06-19 13:21:27</sys_created_on>
        <sys_domain>09ff3d105f231000b12e3572f2b4775d</sys_domain>
        <sys_domain_path>!!!/!!!/</sys_domain_path>
        <sys_id>7587f9fcdb211010280df36f299619b7</sys_id>
        <sys_mod_count>0</sys_mod_count>
        <sys_updated_by>admin</sys_updated_by>
        <sys_updated_on>2020-06-19 13:21:27</sys_updated_on>
        <task_for/>
        <time_worked/>
        <upon_approval>proceed</upon_approval>
        <upon_reject>cancel</upon_reject>
        <urgency>3</urgency>
        <user_input/>
        <variables/>
        <watch_list/>
        <wf_activity/>
        <work_end/>
        <work_notes/>
        <work_notes_list/>
        <work_start/>
    </x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1>
</record_update>
]]></payload>
        <sys_class_name>sys_metadata_link</sys_class_name>
        <sys_created_by>admin</sys_created_by>
        <sys_created_on>2020-06-23 20:26:16</sys_created_on>
        <sys_id>ab1f7b06db251010280df36f299619b4</sys_id>
        <sys_mod_count>0</sys_mod_count>
        <sys_name>MP-05</sys_name>
        <sys_package display_value="Rapid ATO" source="x_415531_rapid_ato">64898e36db501010280df36f29961934</sys_package>
        <sys_policy/>
        <sys_scope display_value="Rapid ATO">64898e36db501010280df36f29961934</sys_scope>
        <sys_update_name>sys_metadata_link_ab1f7b06db251010280df36f299619b4</sys_update_name>
        <sys_updated_by>admin</sys_updated_by>
        <sys_updated_on>2020-06-23 20:26:16</sys_updated_on>
        <tablename>x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1</tablename>
    </sys_metadata_link>
</record_update>
