<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><record_update table="sys_metadata_link">
    <sys_metadata_link action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE">
        <directory>unload</directory>
        <documentkey>76877dfcdb211010280df36f29961916</documentkey>
        <payload><![CDATA[<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><record_update sys_domain="09ff3d105f231000b12e3572f2b4775d" table="x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1">
    <x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1 action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE">
        <active>true</active>
        <activity_due/>
        <additional_assignee_list/>
        <approval>not requested</approval>
        <approval_history/>
        <approval_set/>
        <ars_id display_value="ARS 3.1">43903e93dbcd1010280df36f299619aa</ars_id>
        <assessment_methods_and_objects>Examine: System and information integr</assessment_methods_and_objects>
        <assessment_objective>Determine if the organization has implemented all elements of this control as described in the control statements and implementation standard(s).</assessment_objective>
        <assigned_to/>
        <assignment_group/>
        <assurance/>
        <baseline>High; Moderate; Low</baseline>
        <business_duration/>
        <business_service/>
        <calendar_duration/>
        <close_notes/>
        <closed_at/>
        <closed_by/>
        <cmdb_ci/>
        <comments/>
        <comments_and_work_notes/>
        <company/>
        <contact_type/>
        <contract/>
        <control_definition>The organization: a. Employs malicious code protection mechanisms at information system entry and exit points to detect and eradicate malicious code; b. Updates malicious code protection mechanisms whenever new releases are available in accordance with CMS configuration management policy and procedures; andc. Configures malicious code protection mechanisms to:   1. Perform periodic scans of the information system using the frequency specified in Implementation Standard 1 and Implementation Standard 2, and real-time scans of files from external sources at endpoint, and/or network entry/exit points, as the files are downloaded, opened, or executed in accordance with organizational security policy; and   2. Block and quarantine malicious code and send alert to administrator in response to malicious code detection; and d. Addresses the receipt of false positives during malicious code detection and eradication and the resulting potential impact on the availability of the information system.</control_definition>
        <control_family display_value="System and Information Integrity">aa873dfcdb211010280df36f299619f4</control_family>
        <control_name>Malicious Code Protection</control_name>
        <control_number>SI-03</control_number>
        <control_type>Mandatory</control_type>
        <correlation_display/>
        <correlation_id/>
        <delivery_plan/>
        <delivery_task/>
        <description/>
        <due_date/>
        <escalation>0</escalation>
        <expected_start/>
        <follow_up/>
        <group_id>SI-03</group_id>
        <group_list/>
        <high>true</high>
        <impact>3</impact>
        <implementation_standards>High, Moderate &amp; Low:&#13;
&#13;
Std.1 - Desktop malicious code scanning software is configured to perform critical system file scans no less often than once every twelve (12) hours and full system scans no l</implementation_standards>
        <knowledge>false</knowledge>
        <location/>
        <low>true</low>
        <made_sla>true</made_sla>
        <moderate>true</moderate>
        <number>ARSC0011195</number>
        <opened_at>2020-06-19 13:21:31</opened_at>
        <opened_by display_value="System Administrator">6816f79cc0a8016401c5a33be04be441</opened_by>
        <order/>
        <parent/>
        <priority>3</priority>
        <reassignment_count>0</reassignment_count>
        <reference_policy>FedRAMP Rev. 4 Baseline; FISCAM: AS-3, CM-5; NIST SP: 800-37, 800-39, 800-83, 800-137; OMB Memo: M-14-03, M-15-01, M-16-04; 45 C.F.R. ยง164.308(a)(5)(ii)(B); 45 C.F.R. ยง164.308(a)(6)(ii)</reference_policy>
        <rejection_goto/>
        <related_controls>CM-3, MP-2, SA-4, SA-8, SA-12, SA-13, SC</related_controls>
        <service_offering/>
        <short_description/>
        <sla_due/>
        <standard>NIST-800</standard>
        <state>1</state>
        <supplemental_guidance>Information system entry and exit points include, for example, firewalls, electronic mail servers, web servers, proxy servers, remote-access servers, workstations, notebook computers, and mobile devices. Malicious code includes, for example, viruses, worms, Trojan horses, and spyware. Malicious code can also be encoded in various formats (e.g., UUENCODE, Unicode), contained within compressed or hidden files, or hidden in files using steganography. Malicious code can be transported by different means, including, for example, web accesses, electronic mail, electronic mail attachments, and portable storage devices. Malicious code insertions occur through the exploitation of information system vulnerabilities. Malicious code protection mechanisms include, for example, anti-virus signature definitions and reputation-based technologies. A variety of technologies and methods exist to limit or eliminate the effects of malicious code. Pervasive configuration management and comprehensive software integrity controls may be effective in preventing execution of unauthorized code. In addition to commercial off-the-shelf software, malicious code may also be present in custom-built software. This could include, for example, logic bombs, back doors, and other types of cyber-attacks that could affect organizational missions/business functions. Traditional malicious code protection mechanisms cannot always detect such code. In these situations, organizations rely instead on other safeguards, including, for example, secure coding practices, configuration management and control, trusted procurement processes, and monitoring practices to help ensure that software does not perform functions other than the functions intended. Organizations may determine that in response to the detection of malicious code, different actions may be warranted. For example, organizations can define actions in response to malicious code detection during periodic scans, actions in response to detection of malicious downloads, and/or actions in response to detection of maliciousness when attempting to open or execute files.&#13;
&#13;
Guidance for systems processing, storing, or transmitting PHI:&#13;
&#13;
Malicious code protections are essential in system with PHI because of the sensitivity and desirability of such information.Under the HIPAA Security Rule, this is an addressable implementation specification. HIPAA covered entities must conduct an analysis as described at 45 C.F.R. ยง 164.306 (Security standards: General rules) part (d) (Implementation specifications) to determine how it must be applied within the organization.</supplemental_guidance>
        <sys_class_name>x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1</sys_class_name>
        <sys_created_by>admin</sys_created_by>
        <sys_created_on>2020-06-19 13:21:31</sys_created_on>
        <sys_domain>09ff3d105f231000b12e3572f2b4775d</sys_domain>
        <sys_domain_path>!!!/!!!/</sys_domain_path>
        <sys_id>76877dfcdb211010280df36f29961916</sys_id>
        <sys_mod_count>0</sys_mod_count>
        <sys_updated_by>admin</sys_updated_by>
        <sys_updated_on>2020-06-19 13:21:31</sys_updated_on>
        <task_for/>
        <time_worked/>
        <upon_approval>proceed</upon_approval>
        <upon_reject>cancel</upon_reject>
        <urgency>3</urgency>
        <user_input/>
        <variables/>
        <watch_list/>
        <wf_activity/>
        <work_end/>
        <work_notes/>
        <work_notes_list/>
        <work_start/>
    </x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1>
</record_update>
]]></payload>
        <sys_class_name>sys_metadata_link</sys_class_name>
        <sys_created_by>admin</sys_created_by>
        <sys_created_on>2020-06-23 20:26:16</sys_created_on>
        <sys_id>6f1f7b06db251010280df36f299619c4</sys_id>
        <sys_mod_count>0</sys_mod_count>
        <sys_name>SI-03</sys_name>
        <sys_package display_value="Rapid ATO" source="x_415531_rapid_ato">64898e36db501010280df36f29961934</sys_package>
        <sys_policy/>
        <sys_scope display_value="Rapid ATO">64898e36db501010280df36f29961934</sys_scope>
        <sys_update_name>sys_metadata_link_6f1f7b06db251010280df36f299619c4</sys_update_name>
        <sys_updated_by>admin</sys_updated_by>
        <sys_updated_on>2020-06-23 20:26:16</sys_updated_on>
        <tablename>x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1</tablename>
    </sys_metadata_link>
</record_update>
