<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><record_update table="sys_metadata_link">
    <sys_metadata_link action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE">
        <directory>unload</directory>
        <documentkey>96873dfcdb211010280df36f2996193b</documentkey>
        <payload><![CDATA[<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><record_update sys_domain="09ff3d105f231000b12e3572f2b4775d" table="x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1">
    <x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1 action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE">
        <active>true</active>
        <activity_due/>
        <additional_assignee_list/>
        <approval>not requested</approval>
        <approval_history/>
        <approval_set/>
        <ars_id display_value="ARS 3.1">43903e93dbcd1010280df36f299619aa</ars_id>
        <assessment_methods_and_objects>Examine: System and services acquisiti</assessment_methods_and_objects>
        <assessment_objective>Determine if the organization has implemented all elements of this control as described in the control statements and implementation standard(s).</assessment_objective>
        <assigned_to/>
        <assignment_group/>
        <assurance>Assurance</assurance>
        <baseline>High; Moderate; Low</baseline>
        <business_duration/>
        <business_service/>
        <calendar_duration/>
        <close_notes/>
        <closed_at/>
        <closed_by/>
        <cmdb_ci/>
        <comments/>
        <comments_and_work_notes/>
        <company/>
        <contact_type/>
        <contract/>
        <control_definition>The organization: a. Manages the information system using a formally defined and documented system development life cycle (SDLC) process that incorporates information security considerations b. Defines and documents information security roles and responsibilities throughout the system development life cycle; c. Identifies individuals having information system security roles and responsibilities; and d. Integrates the organizational information security risk management process into system development life cycle activities.</control_definition>
        <control_family display_value="System and Services Acquisition">9e873dfcdb211010280df36f29961936</control_family>
        <control_name>System Development Life Cycle</control_name>
        <control_number>SA-03</control_number>
        <control_type>Mandatory</control_type>
        <correlation_display/>
        <correlation_id/>
        <delivery_plan/>
        <delivery_task/>
        <description/>
        <due_date/>
        <escalation>0</escalation>
        <expected_start/>
        <follow_up/>
        <group_id>SA-03</group_id>
        <group_list/>
        <high>true</high>
        <impact>3</impact>
        <implementation_standards>High, Moderate &amp; Low:&#13;
&#13;
Std.1 - The information system must be managed using:  (a) The information security steps of IEEE 12207.0 standard for SDLC, as defined in the CMS eXpedited Life Cycle (XLC), </implementation_standards>
        <knowledge>false</knowledge>
        <location/>
        <low>true</low>
        <made_sla>true</made_sla>
        <moderate>true</moderate>
        <number>ARSC0011123</number>
        <opened_at>2020-06-19 13:21:29</opened_at>
        <opened_by display_value="System Administrator">6816f79cc0a8016401c5a33be04be441</opened_by>
        <order/>
        <parent/>
        <priority>3</priority>
        <reassignment_count>0</reassignment_count>
        <reference_policy>FedRAMP Rev. 4 Baseline; FISCAM: AS-3, CM-3; NIST SP: 800-37, 800-64; OMB Circular A-130:</reference_policy>
        <rejection_goto/>
        <related_controls>AT-3, PM-7, SA-8</related_controls>
        <service_offering/>
        <short_description/>
        <sla_due/>
        <standard>NIST-800</standard>
        <state>1</state>
        <supplemental_guidance>A well-defined system development life cycle provides the foundation for the successful development, implementation, and operation of organizational information systems. To apply the required security controls within the system development life cycle requires a basic understanding of information security, threats, vulnerabilities, adverse impacts, and risk to critical missions/business functions. The security engineering principles in SA-8 cannot be properly applied if individuals that design, code, and test information systems and system components (including information technology products) do not understand security. Therefore, organizations include qualified personnel, for example, chief information security officers, security architects, security engineers, and information system security officers in system development life cycle activities to ensure that security requirements are incorporated into organizational information systems. It is equally important that developers include individuals on the development team that possess the requisite security expertise and skills to ensure that needed security capabilities are effectively integrated into the information system. Security awareness and training programs can help ensure that individuals having key security roles and responsibilities have the appropriate experience, skills, and expertise to conduct assigned system development life cycle activities. The effective integration of security requirements into enterprise architecture also helps to ensure that important security considerations are addressed early in the system development life cycle and that those considerations are directly related to the organizational mission/business processes. This process also facilitates the integration of the information security architecture into the enterprise architecture, consistent with organizational risk management and information security strategies.&#13;
&#13;
Guidance for systems processing, storing, or transmitting PII (to include PHI):&#13;
&#13;
To ensure that privacy and security controls are appropriately considered during each phase of the SDLC, both the security and privacy offices should have a clear understanding of the requirements to protect PII. The privacy office should participate throughout the SDLC.</supplemental_guidance>
        <sys_class_name>x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1</sys_class_name>
        <sys_created_by>admin</sys_created_by>
        <sys_created_on>2020-06-19 13:21:29</sys_created_on>
        <sys_domain>09ff3d105f231000b12e3572f2b4775d</sys_domain>
        <sys_domain_path>!!!/!!!/</sys_domain_path>
        <sys_id>96873dfcdb211010280df36f2996193b</sys_id>
        <sys_mod_count>0</sys_mod_count>
        <sys_updated_by>admin</sys_updated_by>
        <sys_updated_on>2020-06-19 13:21:29</sys_updated_on>
        <task_for/>
        <time_worked/>
        <upon_approval>proceed</upon_approval>
        <upon_reject>cancel</upon_reject>
        <urgency>3</urgency>
        <user_input/>
        <variables/>
        <watch_list/>
        <wf_activity/>
        <work_end/>
        <work_notes/>
        <work_notes_list/>
        <work_start/>
    </x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1>
</record_update>
]]></payload>
        <sys_class_name>sys_metadata_link</sys_class_name>
        <sys_created_by>admin</sys_created_by>
        <sys_created_on>2020-06-23 20:26:21</sys_created_on>
        <sys_id>b02fbb06db251010280df36f2996195f</sys_id>
        <sys_mod_count>0</sys_mod_count>
        <sys_name>SA-03</sys_name>
        <sys_package display_value="Rapid ATO" source="x_415531_rapid_ato">64898e36db501010280df36f29961934</sys_package>
        <sys_policy/>
        <sys_scope display_value="Rapid ATO">64898e36db501010280df36f29961934</sys_scope>
        <sys_update_name>sys_metadata_link_b02fbb06db251010280df36f2996195f</sys_update_name>
        <sys_updated_by>admin</sys_updated_by>
        <sys_updated_on>2020-06-23 20:26:21</sys_updated_on>
        <tablename>x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1</tablename>
    </sys_metadata_link>
</record_update>
