<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><record_update table="sys_metadata_link">
    <sys_metadata_link action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE">
        <directory>unload</directory>
        <documentkey>c387bdfcdb211010280df36f2996191f</documentkey>
        <payload><![CDATA[<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><record_update sys_domain="09ff3d105f231000b12e3572f2b4775d" table="x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1">
    <x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1 action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE">
        <active>true</active>
        <activity_due/>
        <additional_assignee_list/>
        <approval>not requested</approval>
        <approval_history/>
        <approval_set/>
        <ars_id display_value="ARS 3.1">43903e93dbcd1010280df36f299619aa</ars_id>
        <assessment_methods_and_objects>Systems processing, storing, or transm</assessment_methods_and_objects>
        <assessment_objective>Systems processing, storing, or transmitting PII (to include PHI):&#13;
&#13;
Determine if:(i) The organization identifies the minimum PII elements that are relevant and necessary to accomplish the legally authorized purpose of collection;(ii) The organization li</assessment_objective>
        <assigned_to/>
        <assignment_group/>
        <assurance/>
        <baseline>High; Moderate; Low</baseline>
        <business_duration/>
        <business_service/>
        <calendar_duration/>
        <close_notes/>
        <closed_at/>
        <closed_by/>
        <cmdb_ci/>
        <comments/>
        <comments_and_work_notes/>
        <company/>
        <contact_type/>
        <contract/>
        <control_definition>Systems processing, storing, or transmitting PII (to include PHI):&#13;
&#13;
The organization: a. Identifies the minimum PII elements that are relevant and necessary to accomplish the purpose of collection (and where a collection of certain PII requires legal authorization, HHS/CMS must ensure that such collection is legally authorized); b. Limits the collection and retention of PII to the minimum elements identified in the notice and, when the collection of PII is made directly from the subject individual, limits its purposes to those for which the individual has provided consent to the extent permitted by law; and c. Conducts an initial evaluation of PII holdings and establishes and follows a schedule for regularly reviewing those holdings, no less often than once every three hundred sixty-five (365) days, to ensure that only PII identified in the notice is collected and retained, and that the PII continues to be necessary to accomplish the legally authorized purpose.</control_definition>
        <control_family display_value="Data Minimization and Retention">cb87bdfcdb211010280df36f2996191d</control_family>
        <control_name>Minimization of Personally Identifiable Information</control_name>
        <control_number>DM-01</control_number>
        <control_type>Mandatory</control_type>
        <correlation_display/>
        <correlation_id/>
        <delivery_plan/>
        <delivery_task/>
        <description/>
        <due_date/>
        <escalation>0</escalation>
        <expected_start/>
        <follow_up/>
        <group_id>DM-01</group_id>
        <group_list/>
        <high>true</high>
        <impact>3</impact>
        <implementation_standards/>
        <knowledge>false</knowledge>
        <location/>
        <low>true</low>
        <made_sla>true</made_sla>
        <moderate>true</moderate>
        <number>ARSC0011260</number>
        <opened_at>2020-06-19 13:21:33</opened_at>
        <opened_by display_value="System Administrator">6816f79cc0a8016401c5a33be04be441</opened_by>
        <order/>
        <parent/>
        <priority>3</priority>
        <reassignment_count>0</reassignment_count>
        <reference_policy>CFR: 45 C.F.R. §164.502(b); Code: 5 U.S.C. §552a(e)(1); E-Gov: §208(b); OMB Memo: M-03-22, M-17-12; OMB Circular A-130: 7.g. and 8.a.; Privacy Act: §552a(e)</reference_policy>
        <rejection_goto/>
        <related_controls>AP-1, AP-2, AR-4, IP-1, SE-1, SI-12, TR-</related_controls>
        <service_offering/>
        <short_description/>
        <sla_due/>
        <standard>NIST-800</standard>
        <state>1</state>
        <supplemental_guidance>Guidance for systems processing, storing, or transmitting PII (to include PHI):&#13;
&#13;
Coordinating review of the organization’s holdings of PII with existing system review processes maximizes the efficient use of organization resources and will ensure all PII retained, even if the PII is not maintained in a Privacy Act system of records, is relevant and accurate. Reducing PII to the minimum required to accomplish the legally authorized purpose of collection and retaining PII for the minimum necessary period of time reduces the risk of PII breaches and will reduce the risk of the organization making decisions based on inaccurate PII.Organizations take appropriate steps to ensure that the collection of PII is consistent with a purpose authorized by law or regulation. The minimum set of PII elements required to support a specific organization’s business process may be a subset of the PII the organization is authorized to collect. Program officials and program representatives such as Data Guardians consult with the Senior Official for Privacy (SOP) and legal counsel to identify the minimum PII elements required by the information system or activity to accomplish the legally authorized purpose.Organizations can further reduce their privacy and security risks by also reducing their inventory of PII, where appropriate. OMB Memorandum 07-16 requires organizations to conduct both an initial review and subsequent reviews of their holdings of all PII and ensure, to the maximum extent practicable, that such holdings are accurate, relevant, timely, and complete. Organizations are also directed by OMB to reduce their holdings to the minimum necessary for the proper performance of a documented organizational business purpose. OMB Memorandum 17-12 requires organizations to develop and publicize, either through a notice in the Federal Register or on their websites, a schedule for periodic reviews of their holdings to supplement the initial review. Organizations coordinate with their federal records officers to ensure that reductions in organizational holdings of PII are consistent with NARA retention schedules.Organizations should coordinate the PII holdings reviews with the systems’ annual information security reviews schedule to the maximum extent practicable.By performing periodic evaluations, organizations reduce risk, ensure that they are collecting only the data specified in the notice, and ensure that the data collected is still relevant and necessary for the purpose(s) specified in the notice.</supplemental_guidance>
        <sys_class_name>x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1</sys_class_name>
        <sys_created_by>admin</sys_created_by>
        <sys_created_on>2020-06-19 13:21:33</sys_created_on>
        <sys_domain>09ff3d105f231000b12e3572f2b4775d</sys_domain>
        <sys_domain_path>!!!/!!!/</sys_domain_path>
        <sys_id>c387bdfcdb211010280df36f2996191f</sys_id>
        <sys_mod_count>0</sys_mod_count>
        <sys_updated_by>admin</sys_updated_by>
        <sys_updated_on>2020-06-19 13:21:33</sys_updated_on>
        <task_for/>
        <time_worked/>
        <upon_approval>proceed</upon_approval>
        <upon_reject>cancel</upon_reject>
        <urgency>3</urgency>
        <user_input/>
        <variables/>
        <watch_list/>
        <wf_activity/>
        <work_end/>
        <work_notes/>
        <work_notes_list/>
        <work_start/>
    </x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1>
</record_update>
]]></payload>
        <sys_class_name>sys_metadata_link</sys_class_name>
        <sys_created_by>admin</sys_created_by>
        <sys_created_on>2020-06-23 20:26:31</sys_created_on>
        <sys_id>5f2ffb06db251010280df36f29961962</sys_id>
        <sys_mod_count>0</sys_mod_count>
        <sys_name>DM-01</sys_name>
        <sys_package display_value="Rapid ATO" source="x_415531_rapid_ato">64898e36db501010280df36f29961934</sys_package>
        <sys_policy/>
        <sys_scope display_value="Rapid ATO">64898e36db501010280df36f29961934</sys_scope>
        <sys_update_name>sys_metadata_link_5f2ffb06db251010280df36f29961962</sys_update_name>
        <sys_updated_by>admin</sys_updated_by>
        <sys_updated_on>2020-06-23 20:26:31</sys_updated_on>
        <tablename>x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1</tablename>
    </sys_metadata_link>
</record_update>
