<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><record_update table="sys_metadata_link">
    <sys_metadata_link action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE">
        <directory>unload</directory>
        <documentkey>a887b9fcdb211010280df36f29961954</documentkey>
        <payload><![CDATA[<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><record_update sys_domain="09ff3d105f231000b12e3572f2b4775d" table="x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1">
    <x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1 action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE">
        <active>true</active>
        <activity_due/>
        <additional_assignee_list/>
        <approval>not requested</approval>
        <approval_history/>
        <approval_set/>
        <ars_id display_value="ARS 3.1">43903e93dbcd1010280df36f299619aa</ars_id>
        <assessment_methods_and_objects>Examine: Audit and accountability poli</assessment_methods_and_objects>
        <assessment_objective>Determine if the organization has implemented all elements of this control as described in the control statements and implementation standard(s).&#13;
&#13;
Systems defined as CSPs:&#13;
&#13;
Determine if the organization has implemented all elements of this control as </assessment_objective>
        <assigned_to/>
        <assignment_group/>
        <assurance/>
        <baseline>High; Moderate; Low</baseline>
        <business_duration/>
        <business_service/>
        <calendar_duration/>
        <close_notes/>
        <closed_at/>
        <closed_by/>
        <cmdb_ci/>
        <comments/>
        <comments_and_work_notes/>
        <company/>
        <contact_type/>
        <contract/>
        <control_definition>The organization: a. Determines, based on a risk assessment and CMS mission/business needs, that the information system can audit the events specified in Implementation Standard 1; b. Coordinates the security audit function with other organizational entities requiring audit-related information to enhance mutual support and to help guide the selection of auditable events; c. Provides a rationale for why the auditable events are deemed to be adequate (relevant) to support after-the-fact investigations of security and privacy incidents; and d. Determines which events specified in Implementation Standard 2 require auditing on a continuous basis in response to specific situations.</control_definition>
        <control_family display_value="Audit and Accountability">6887b9fcdb211010280df36f29961951</control_family>
        <control_name>Audit Events</control_name>
        <control_number>AU-02</control_number>
        <control_type>Mandatory</control_type>
        <correlation_display/>
        <correlation_id/>
        <delivery_plan/>
        <delivery_task/>
        <description/>
        <due_date/>
        <escalation>0</escalation>
        <expected_start/>
        <follow_up/>
        <group_id>AU-02</group_id>
        <group_list/>
        <high>true</high>
        <impact>3</impact>
        <implementation_standards>High &amp; Moderate:&#13;
&#13;
Std.1 - List of auditable events:  (a) Server alerts and error messages;  (b) User log-on and log-off (successful or unsuccessful);  (c) All system administration activities;  (d) </implementation_standards>
        <knowledge>false</knowledge>
        <location/>
        <low>true</low>
        <made_sla>true</made_sla>
        <moderate>true</moderate>
        <number>ARSC0010861</number>
        <opened_at>2020-06-19 13:21:22</opened_at>
        <opened_by display_value="System Administrator">6816f79cc0a8016401c5a33be04be441</opened_by>
        <order/>
        <parent/>
        <priority>3</priority>
        <reassignment_count>0</reassignment_count>
        <reference_policy>FedRAMP Rev. 4 Baseline; FISCAM: AC-5, AS-2; HIPAA: 45 C.F.R. §164.308(a)(5)(ii)(C), 45 C.F.R. §164.312(b), 45 C.F.R. §164.308(a)(1)(ii)(D); 45 C.F.R; NIST SP: 800-37, 800-39, 800-92, 800-137; OMB Memo: M-14-03, M-15-01, M-16-04, M-06-16, M-17-12; OMB Circular A-130, 7.g., 8.b(2)(c)(iii) and Appendix I; Web: csrc.nist.gov/pcig/cig.html</reference_policy>
        <rejection_goto/>
        <related_controls>AC-6, AC-17, AR-4, AU-3, AU-12, MA-4, MP</related_controls>
        <service_offering/>
        <short_description/>
        <sla_due/>
        <standard>NIST-800</standard>
        <state>1</state>
        <supplemental_guidance>An event is any observable occurrence in an organizational information system. Organizations identify audit events as those events which are significant and relevant to the security of information systems and the environments in which those systems operate to meet specific and ongoing audit needs. Audit events can include, for example, password changes, failed logons, or failed accesses related to information systems, administrative privilege usage, PIV credential usage, or third-party credential usage. In determining the set of auditable events, organizations consider the auditing appropriate for each of the security controls to be implemented. To balance auditing requirements with other information system needs, this control also requires identifying that subset of auditable events that are audited at a given point in time. For example, organizations may determine that information systems must have the capability to log every file access both successful and unsuccessful, but not activate that capability except for specific circumstances due to the potential burden on system performance. Auditing requirements, including the need for auditable events, may be referenced in other security controls and control enhancements. Organizations also include auditable events that are required by applicable federal laws, Executive Orders, directives, policies, regulations, and standards. Audit records can be generated at various levels of abstraction, including at the packet level as information traverses the network. Selecting the appropriate level of abstraction is a critical aspect of an audit capability and can facilitate the identification of root causes to problems. Organizations consider in the definition of auditable events, the auditing necessary to cover related events such as the steps in distributed, transaction-based processes (e.g., processes that are distributed across multiple organizations) and actions that occur in service-oriented architectures.The Federal Rules of Evidence can be found at this website: http://www.uscourts.gov/file/rules-evidence  &#13;
&#13;
Guidance for systems processing, storing, or transmitting PII (to include PHI):&#13;
&#13;
This control identifies privacy-relevant security auditable events using a risk-based approach. Examples of privacy-relevant auditable events include logging access to or modification of PII.The parameter values for this control do not provide an exhaustive list of all auditable events, but instead list the auditable events required by OMB privacy policy. The organization should manage the length of time that a log file is maintained to the period necessary to comply with the organization’s security and privacy policies.&#13;
&#13;
Guidance for systems processing, storing, or transmitting PHI:&#13;
&#13;
The HIPAA Security Rule requires the auditing of activity in information systems that contain PHI but does not identify the specific audit events. Follow PII Supplemental Guidance.</supplemental_guidance>
        <sys_class_name>x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1</sys_class_name>
        <sys_created_by>admin</sys_created_by>
        <sys_created_on>2020-06-19 13:21:22</sys_created_on>
        <sys_domain>09ff3d105f231000b12e3572f2b4775d</sys_domain>
        <sys_domain_path>!!!/!!!/</sys_domain_path>
        <sys_id>a887b9fcdb211010280df36f29961954</sys_id>
        <sys_mod_count>0</sys_mod_count>
        <sys_updated_by>admin</sys_updated_by>
        <sys_updated_on>2020-06-19 13:21:22</sys_updated_on>
        <task_for/>
        <time_worked/>
        <upon_approval>proceed</upon_approval>
        <upon_reject>cancel</upon_reject>
        <urgency>3</urgency>
        <user_input/>
        <variables/>
        <watch_list/>
        <wf_activity/>
        <work_end/>
        <work_notes/>
        <work_notes_list/>
        <work_start/>
    </x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1>
</record_update>
]]></payload>
        <sys_class_name>sys_metadata_link</sys_class_name>
        <sys_created_by>admin</sys_created_by>
        <sys_created_on>2020-06-23 20:26:25</sys_created_on>
        <sys_id>7d2fbb06db251010280df36f299619d6</sys_id>
        <sys_mod_count>0</sys_mod_count>
        <sys_name>AU-02</sys_name>
        <sys_package display_value="Rapid ATO" source="x_415531_rapid_ato">64898e36db501010280df36f29961934</sys_package>
        <sys_policy/>
        <sys_scope display_value="Rapid ATO">64898e36db501010280df36f29961934</sys_scope>
        <sys_update_name>sys_metadata_link_7d2fbb06db251010280df36f299619d6</sys_update_name>
        <sys_updated_by>admin</sys_updated_by>
        <sys_updated_on>2020-06-23 20:26:25</sys_updated_on>
        <tablename>x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1</tablename>
    </sys_metadata_link>
</record_update>
