<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><record_update table="sys_metadata_link">
    <sys_metadata_link action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE">
        <directory>unload</directory>
        <documentkey>03877dfcdb211010280df36f299619f6</documentkey>
        <payload><![CDATA[<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><record_update sys_domain="09ff3d105f231000b12e3572f2b4775d" table="x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1">
    <x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1 action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE">
        <active>true</active>
        <activity_due/>
        <additional_assignee_list/>
        <approval>not requested</approval>
        <approval_history/>
        <approval_set/>
        <ars_id display_value="ARS 3.1">43903e93dbcd1010280df36f299619aa</ars_id>
        <assessment_methods_and_objects>Examine: Organization privacy policy m</assessment_methods_and_objects>
        <assessment_objective>Determine if the organization monitors and audits privacy controls and internal privacy policy as required to confirm effective implementation.Determine if the system captures all requests to update personally identifiable information (PII) in the system </assessment_objective>
        <assigned_to/>
        <assignment_group/>
        <assurance/>
        <baseline>High; Moderate; Low</baseline>
        <business_duration/>
        <business_service/>
        <calendar_duration/>
        <close_notes/>
        <closed_at/>
        <closed_by/>
        <cmdb_ci/>
        <comments/>
        <comments_and_work_notes/>
        <company/>
        <contact_type/>
        <contract/>
        <control_definition>The organization a. Monitors and audits privacy controls no less often than once every 365 days to ensure effective implementation; andb. Monitors for changes to applicable privacy laws, regulations, and policy affecting internal privacy policy no less often than once every 365 days to ensure internal privacy policy remains effective; andc. Documents, tracks, and ensures mitigation of corrective actions identified through monitoring or auditing.</control_definition>
        <control_family display_value="Accountability, Audit, and Risk Manage">c7877dfcdb211010280df36f299619d2</control_family>
        <control_name>Privacy Monitoring and Auditing</control_name>
        <control_number>AR-04</control_number>
        <control_type>Mandatory</control_type>
        <correlation_display/>
        <correlation_id/>
        <delivery_plan/>
        <delivery_task/>
        <description/>
        <due_date/>
        <escalation>0</escalation>
        <expected_start/>
        <follow_up/>
        <group_id>AR-04</group_id>
        <group_list/>
        <high>true</high>
        <impact>3</impact>
        <implementation_standards/>
        <knowledge>false</knowledge>
        <location/>
        <low>true</low>
        <made_sla>true</made_sla>
        <moderate>true</moderate>
        <number>ARSC0011248</number>
        <opened_at>2020-06-19 13:21:32</opened_at>
        <opened_by display_value="System Administrator">6816f79cc0a8016401c5a33be04be441</opened_by>
        <order/>
        <parent/>
        <priority>3</priority>
        <reassignment_count>0</reassignment_count>
        <reference_policy>Code: 44 U.S.C.: ยง3541; E-Gov: ยง208; OMB Memo: M-03-22, M-05-08, M-06-16, M-17-12; OMB Circular A-130; Privacy Act: ยง552a; 45 C.F.R. ยง164.530(a)(1)(ii)</reference_policy>
        <rejection_goto/>
        <related_controls>AR-6, AR-7, AU-1, AU-2, AU-3, AU-6, AU-1</related_controls>
        <service_offering/>
        <short_description/>
        <sla_due/>
        <standard>NIST-800</standard>
        <state>1</state>
        <supplemental_guidance>Monitoring and auditing activities ensure privacy controls are implemented and operating effectively.To promote accountability, organizations identify and address gaps in privacy compliance, management, operational, and technical controls by conducting regular assessments (e.g., internal risk assessments). These assessments can be self-assessments or third-party audits that result in reports on compliance gaps identified in programs, projects, and information systems. In addition to auditing for effective implementation of all privacy controls identified in [800-53 Appendix J], organizations assess whether they: (i) implement a process to embed privacy considerations into the life cycle of personally identifiable information (PII), programs, information systems, mission/business processes, and technology; (ii) monitor for changes to applicable privacy laws, regulations, and policies; (iii) track programs, information systems, and applications that collect and maintain PII to ensure compliance; (iv) ensure that access to PII is only on a need-to-know basis; and (v) ensure that PII is being maintained and used only for the legally authorized purposes identified in the public notice(s).Organizations also: (i) implement technology to audit for the security, appropriate use, and loss of PII; (ii) perform reviews to ensure physical security of documents containing PII; (iii) assess contractor compliance with privacy requirements; and (iv) ensure that corrective actions identified as part of the assessment process are tracked and monitored until audit findings are corrected. The Senior Official for Privacy (SOP) coordinates monitoring and auditing efforts with information security officials and ensures that the results are provided to senior managers and oversight officials.Where security and privacy controls align, to achieve the most efficient and effective implementation, the CMS SOP/CPO and CIO or CISO should coordinate to develop a single organizational process to conduct audit and monitoring.</supplemental_guidance>
        <sys_class_name>x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1</sys_class_name>
        <sys_created_by>admin</sys_created_by>
        <sys_created_on>2020-06-19 13:21:32</sys_created_on>
        <sys_domain>09ff3d105f231000b12e3572f2b4775d</sys_domain>
        <sys_domain_path>!!!/!!!/</sys_domain_path>
        <sys_id>03877dfcdb211010280df36f299619f6</sys_id>
        <sys_mod_count>1</sys_mod_count>
        <sys_updated_by>admin</sys_updated_by>
        <sys_updated_on>2020-06-22 16:06:48</sys_updated_on>
        <task_for/>
        <time_worked/>
        <upon_approval>proceed</upon_approval>
        <upon_reject>cancel</upon_reject>
        <urgency>3</urgency>
        <user_input/>
        <variables/>
        <watch_list/>
        <wf_activity/>
        <work_end/>
        <work_notes/>
        <work_notes_list/>
        <work_start/>
    </x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1>
</record_update>
]]></payload>
        <sys_class_name>sys_metadata_link</sys_class_name>
        <sys_created_by>admin</sys_created_by>
        <sys_created_on>2020-06-23 20:26:01</sys_created_on>
        <sys_id>bb0ff706db251010280df36f2996199b</sys_id>
        <sys_mod_count>0</sys_mod_count>
        <sys_name>AR-04</sys_name>
        <sys_package display_value="Rapid ATO" source="x_415531_rapid_ato">64898e36db501010280df36f29961934</sys_package>
        <sys_policy/>
        <sys_scope display_value="Rapid ATO">64898e36db501010280df36f29961934</sys_scope>
        <sys_update_name>sys_metadata_link_bb0ff706db251010280df36f2996199b</sys_update_name>
        <sys_updated_by>admin</sys_updated_by>
        <sys_updated_on>2020-06-23 20:26:01</sys_updated_on>
        <tablename>x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1</tablename>
    </sys_metadata_link>
</record_update>
