<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><record_update table="sys_metadata_link">
    <sys_metadata_link action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE">
        <directory>unload</directory>
        <documentkey>06873dfcdb211010280df36f29961920</documentkey>
        <payload><![CDATA[<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><record_update sys_domain="09ff3d105f231000b12e3572f2b4775d" table="x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1">
    <x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1 action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE">
        <active>true</active>
        <activity_due/>
        <additional_assignee_list/>
        <approval>not requested</approval>
        <approval_history/>
        <approval_set/>
        <ars_id display_value="ARS 3.1">43903e93dbcd1010280df36f299619aa</ars_id>
        <assessment_methods_and_objects>Examine: Risk assessment policy; secur</assessment_methods_and_objects>
        <assessment_objective>Determine if the organization has implemented all elements of this control as described in the control statements and implementation standard(s).&#13;
&#13;
Systems processing, storing, or transmitting PII (to include PHI):&#13;
&#13;
Determine if the organization has im</assessment_objective>
        <assigned_to/>
        <assignment_group/>
        <assurance>Assurance</assurance>
        <baseline>High; Moderate; Low</baseline>
        <business_duration/>
        <business_service/>
        <calendar_duration/>
        <close_notes/>
        <closed_at/>
        <closed_by/>
        <cmdb_ci/>
        <comments/>
        <comments_and_work_notes/>
        <company/>
        <contact_type/>
        <contract/>
        <control_definition>The organization: a. Conducts an assessment of risk, including the likelihood and magnitude of harm, from the unauthorized access, use, disclosure, disruption, modification, or destruction of the information system and the information it processes, stores, or transmits; b. Conducts an E-Authentication Risk Assessment (ERA), as required, on systems and determines e-authentication assurance levels;c. Documents risk assessment results in the applicable security plan; d. Reviews risk assessment results within every 365 days; e. Disseminates risk assessment results to affected stakeholders, Business Owners(s), and the CMS CISO; and f. Updates the risk assessment before issuing a new authority to operate (ATO) package or within every three (3) years, whichever comes first; or whenever there are significant changes to the information system or environment of operation (including the identification of new threats and vulnerabilities), or other conditions that may impact the security or authorization state of the system.&#13;
&#13;
Systems processing, storing, or transmitting PII (to include PHI):&#13;
&#13;
Include an assessment of the potential risks and vulnerabilities to the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of personally identifiable information (PII) in the related risk assessment documentation.&#13;
&#13;
Systems processing, storing, or transmitting PHI:&#13;
&#13;
The organization documents risk assessment results in a HIPAA Risk Analysis, and associated risks to PHI must be identified within the overall risk assessment. All risk assessment documentation must reflect these findings. All HIPAA Risk Analysis documentation must be maintained for 6 years from the date of creation or date it was last in effect – whichever is later.</control_definition>
        <control_family display_value="Risk Assessment">0e873dfcdb211010280df36f2996191b</control_family>
        <control_name>Risk Assessment</control_name>
        <control_number>RA-03</control_number>
        <control_type>Mandatory</control_type>
        <correlation_display/>
        <correlation_id/>
        <delivery_plan/>
        <delivery_task/>
        <description/>
        <due_date/>
        <escalation>0</escalation>
        <expected_start/>
        <follow_up/>
        <group_id>RA-03</group_id>
        <group_list/>
        <high>true</high>
        <impact>3</impact>
        <implementation_standards>Systems defined as CSPs:&#13;
&#13;
High, Moderate &amp; Low:&#13;
&#13;
CSP.1 - For CSPs, the organization documents risk assessment results in the security assessment report. CSP.2 - For CSPs, the organization reviews </implementation_standards>
        <knowledge>false</knowledge>
        <location/>
        <low>true</low>
        <made_sla>true</made_sla>
        <moderate>true</moderate>
        <number>ARSC0011114</number>
        <opened_at>2020-06-19 13:21:28</opened_at>
        <opened_by display_value="System Administrator">6816f79cc0a8016401c5a33be04be441</opened_by>
        <order/>
        <parent/>
        <priority>3</priority>
        <reassignment_count>0</reassignment_count>
        <reference_policy/>
        <rejection_goto/>
        <related_controls>RA-2, PM-9, AR-2</related_controls>
        <service_offering/>
        <short_description/>
        <sla_due/>
        <standard>NIST-800</standard>
        <state>1</state>
        <supplemental_guidance>Clearly defined authorization boundaries are a prerequisite for effective risk assessments. Risk assessments consider threats, vulnerabilities, likelihood, and impact to organizational operations and assets, individuals, other organizations, and the Nation based on the operation and use of information systems. Risk assessments also consider risk from external parties (e.g., service providers, contractors operating information systems on behalf of the organization, individuals accessing organizational information systems, outsourcing entities). In accordance with OMB policy and related E-authentication initiatives, authentication of public users accessing federal information systems may also be required to protect nonpublic or privacy-related information. As such, organizational assessments of risk also address public access to federal information systems.Risk assessments (either formal or informal) can be conducted at all three tiers in the risk management hierarchy (i.e., organization level, mission/business process level, or information system level) and at any phase in the system development life cycle. Risk assessments can also be conducted at various steps in the Risk Management Framework, including categorization, security control selection, security control implementation, security control assessment, information system authorization, and security control monitoring. RA-3 is noteworthy in that the control must be partially implemented prior to the implementation of other controls to complete the first two steps in the Risk Management Framework. Risk assessments can play an important role in security control selection processes, particularly during the application of tailoring guidance, which includes security control supplementation.&#13;
&#13;
Guidance for systems processing, storing, or transmitting PII (to include PHI):&#13;
&#13;
A standardized risk assessment process should include a consideration of risks associated with the collection, maintenance, and use of sensitive information such as PII. Effective implementation of privacy risk management processes requires both organizational and information system processes across the life cycle of the mission, business processes, and information system. An evaluation of privacy risk for an information system benefits an organization and the individuals whose PII are included by enabling the organization to identify, evaluate, and manage the privacy risks for the information in that system. The content of the privacy risk assessment performed under this control should be addressed in concert with the privacy risk evaluation conducted through the internal risk management process to ensure privacy risks are identified, evaluated, and managed in information systems containing privacy-related sensitive information. A standardized risk assessment process should include a consideration of risks associated with the collection, maintenance, and use of sensitive information such as PII. An evaluation of risks associated with the potential impact of loss of the PII must be identified within the overall risk assessment. All risk assessment documentation must reflect these findings.Effective implementation of privacy risk management processes requires both organizational and information system processes across the life cycle of the mission, business processes, and information system. An evaluation of privacy risk for an information system benefits an organization and the individuals whose PII are included by enabling the organization to identify, evaluate, and manage the privacy risks for the information in that system. The content of the privacy risk assessment performed under this control should be addressed in concert with the privacy risk evaluation conducted through the internal risk management process to ensure privacy risks are identified, evaluated, and managed in information systems containing privacy-related sensitive information.&#13;
&#13;
Guidance for systems processing, storing, or transmitting PHI:&#13;
&#13;
The Department of Health and Human Services has issued Final Guidance on Risk Analysis (Assessment) under the HIPAA Security Rule (see  HYPERLINK "http://www.hhs.gov/sites/default/files/ocr/privacy/hipaa/administrative/securityrule/rafinalguidancepdf.pdf" ).</supplemental_guidance>
        <sys_class_name>x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1</sys_class_name>
        <sys_created_by>admin</sys_created_by>
        <sys_created_on>2020-06-19 13:21:28</sys_created_on>
        <sys_domain>09ff3d105f231000b12e3572f2b4775d</sys_domain>
        <sys_domain_path>!!!/!!!/</sys_domain_path>
        <sys_id>06873dfcdb211010280df36f29961920</sys_id>
        <sys_mod_count>0</sys_mod_count>
        <sys_updated_by>admin</sys_updated_by>
        <sys_updated_on>2020-06-19 13:21:28</sys_updated_on>
        <task_for/>
        <time_worked/>
        <upon_approval>proceed</upon_approval>
        <upon_reject>cancel</upon_reject>
        <urgency>3</urgency>
        <user_input/>
        <variables/>
        <watch_list/>
        <wf_activity/>
        <work_end/>
        <work_notes/>
        <work_notes_list/>
        <work_start/>
    </x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1>
</record_update>
]]></payload>
        <sys_class_name>sys_metadata_link</sys_class_name>
        <sys_created_by>admin</sys_created_by>
        <sys_created_on>2020-06-23 20:26:01</sys_created_on>
        <sys_id>c01ff706db251010280df36f299619b5</sys_id>
        <sys_mod_count>0</sys_mod_count>
        <sys_name>RA-03</sys_name>
        <sys_package display_value="Rapid ATO" source="x_415531_rapid_ato">64898e36db501010280df36f29961934</sys_package>
        <sys_policy/>
        <sys_scope display_value="Rapid ATO">64898e36db501010280df36f29961934</sys_scope>
        <sys_update_name>sys_metadata_link_c01ff706db251010280df36f299619b5</sys_update_name>
        <sys_updated_by>admin</sys_updated_by>
        <sys_updated_on>2020-06-23 20:26:01</sys_updated_on>
        <tablename>x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1</tablename>
    </sys_metadata_link>
</record_update>
