<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><record_update table="sys_metadata_link">
    <sys_metadata_link action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE">
        <directory>unload</directory>
        <documentkey>1587f9fcdb211010280df36f29961952</documentkey>
        <payload><![CDATA[<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><record_update sys_domain="09ff3d105f231000b12e3572f2b4775d" table="x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1">
    <x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1 action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE">
        <active>true</active>
        <activity_due/>
        <additional_assignee_list/>
        <approval>not requested</approval>
        <approval_history/>
        <approval_set/>
        <ars_id display_value="ARS 3.1">43903e93dbcd1010280df36f299619aa</ars_id>
        <assessment_methods_and_objects>Examine: Identification and authentica</assessment_methods_and_objects>
        <assessment_objective>Determine if the organization has implemented all elements of this control as described in the control statements and implementation standard(s).</assessment_objective>
        <assigned_to/>
        <assignment_group/>
        <assurance/>
        <baseline>High; Moderate; Low</baseline>
        <business_duration/>
        <business_service/>
        <calendar_duration/>
        <close_notes/>
        <closed_at/>
        <closed_by/>
        <cmdb_ci/>
        <comments/>
        <comments_and_work_notes/>
        <company/>
        <contact_type/>
        <contract/>
        <control_definition>Non-standard account-authenticator management specifications are addressed in the CMS RMH, Volume III, Standard 4.3, Non-Standard Authenticator Management. For all others, the organization manages information system authenticators by: a. Verifying, as part of the initial authenticator distribution, the identity of the individual, group, role, or device receiving the authenticator; b. Establishing initial authenticator content for authenticators defined by the organization; c. Ensuring that authenticators have sufficient strength of mechanism for their intended use; d. Establishing and implementing administrative procedures for initial authenticator distribution, for lost/compromised or damaged authenticators, and for revoking authenticators; e. Changing default content of authenticators prior to information system installation; f. Establishing minimum and maximum lifetime restrictions and reuse conditions for authenticators; g. Changing/refreshing authenticators as follows:    - Passwords are valid for no longer than the period directed in IA-5(1) immediately in the event of known or suspected compromise, and immediately upon system installation (e.g. default or vendor-supplied passwords);    - PIV compliant access cards are valid for no longer than five (5) years;    - PKI certificates issued in accordance with the Federal PKI Common Policy are valid for no longer than three (3) years; and   - Any PKI authentication request must be validated by Online Certificate Status Protocol (OCSP) or Certificate Revocation List (CRL) to ensure that the certificate being used for authentication has not been revoked.h. Protecting authenticator content from unauthorized disclosure and modification; i. Requiring individuals to take, and having devices implement, specific security safeguards to protect authenticators; and j. Changing authenticators for group/role accounts when membership to those accounts changes.</control_definition>
        <control_family display_value="Identification and Authentication">9587f9fcdb211010280df36f2996193a</control_family>
        <control_name>Authenticator Management</control_name>
        <control_number>IA-05</control_number>
        <control_type>Mandatory</control_type>
        <correlation_display/>
        <correlation_id/>
        <delivery_plan/>
        <delivery_task/>
        <description/>
        <due_date/>
        <escalation>0</escalation>
        <expected_start/>
        <follow_up/>
        <group_id>IA-05</group_id>
        <group_list/>
        <high>true</high>
        <impact>3</impact>
        <implementation_standards>Systems defined as CSPs:&#13;
&#13;
High, Moderate &amp; Low:&#13;
&#13;
CSP.1 - For CSPs, the organization manages information system authenticators for users and devices by changing/refreshing authenticators every sixt</implementation_standards>
        <knowledge>false</knowledge>
        <location/>
        <low>true</low>
        <made_sla>true</made_sla>
        <moderate>true</moderate>
        <number>ARSC0010997</number>
        <opened_at>2020-06-19 13:21:25</opened_at>
        <opened_by display_value="System Administrator">6816f79cc0a8016401c5a33be04be441</opened_by>
        <order/>
        <parent/>
        <priority>3</priority>
        <reassignment_count>0</reassignment_count>
        <reference_policy>FedRAMP Rev. 4 Baseline; FIPS Pub: 201; FISCAM: AC-2, AS-2; HIPAA: 45 C.F.R. §164.308(a)(5)(ii)(D); NIST SP: 800-63, 800-73, 800-76, 800-78; OMB Memo: M-04-04, M-11-11; Web: idmanagement.gov; 45 C.F.R. §164.308(a)(3); 45 C.F.R. §164.308(a)(5)(ii)(D); 45 C.F.R. §164.312(d)</reference_policy>
        <rejection_goto/>
        <related_controls>AC-2, AC-3, AC-6, CM-6, IA-2, IA-4, IA-8</related_controls>
        <service_offering/>
        <short_description/>
        <sla_due/>
        <standard>NIST-800</standard>
        <state>1</state>
        <supplemental_guidance>Individual authenticators include, for example, passwords, tokens, biometrics, PKI certificates, and key cards. Initial authenticator content is the actual content (e.g., the initial password) as opposed to requirements about authenticator content (e.g., minimum password length). In many cases, developers ship information system components with factory default authentication credentials to allow for initial installation and configuration. Default authentication credentials are often well-known, easily discoverable, and present a significant security risk. The requirement to protect individual authenticators may be implemented via control PL-4 or PS-6 for authenticators in the possession of individuals and by controls AC-3, AC-6, and SC-28 for authenticators stored within organizational information systems (e.g., passwords stored in hashed or encrypted formats, files containing encrypted or hashed passwords accessible with administrator privileges). Information systems support individual authenticator management by organization-defined settings and restrictions for various authenticator characteristics including, for example, minimum password length, password composition, validation time window for time synchronous one-time tokens, and number of allowed rejections during the verification stage of biometric authentication. Specific actions that can be taken to safeguard authenticators include, for example, maintaining possession of individual authenticators, not loaning or sharing individual authenticators with others, and reporting lost, stolen, or compromised authenticators immediately. Authenticator management includes issuing and revoking, when no longer needed, authenticators for temporary access such as that required for remote maintenance. Device authenticators include, for example, certificates and passwords.&#13;
&#13;
Guidance for systems processing, storing, or transmitting PII (to include PHI):&#13;
&#13;
Adequate security to ensure confidentiality for an information system containing sensitive information such as personally identifiable information (PII) is achieved through the management of the authenticators permitting access to that system. Authenticator management includes periodically changing passwords or other identifiers (e.g., certification and signatures) to reinforce identity validation and adherence to administrative security policies as well as enforces a time-based restriction on access, all of which bound access to PII in some way, limiting exposure in the event a user account is compromised.&#13;
&#13;
Guidance for systems processing, storing, or transmitting PHI:&#13;
&#13;
Under the HIPAA Security Rule, this is an addressable implementation specification. HIPAA covered entities must conduct an analysis as described at 45 C.F.R. § 164.306 (Security standards: General rules) part (d) (Implementation specifications) to determine how it must be applied within the organization.</supplemental_guidance>
        <sys_class_name>x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1</sys_class_name>
        <sys_created_by>admin</sys_created_by>
        <sys_created_on>2020-06-19 13:21:25</sys_created_on>
        <sys_domain>09ff3d105f231000b12e3572f2b4775d</sys_domain>
        <sys_domain_path>!!!/!!!/</sys_domain_path>
        <sys_id>1587f9fcdb211010280df36f29961952</sys_id>
        <sys_mod_count>0</sys_mod_count>
        <sys_updated_by>admin</sys_updated_by>
        <sys_updated_on>2020-06-19 13:21:25</sys_updated_on>
        <task_for/>
        <time_worked/>
        <upon_approval>proceed</upon_approval>
        <upon_reject>cancel</upon_reject>
        <urgency>3</urgency>
        <user_input/>
        <variables/>
        <watch_list/>
        <wf_activity/>
        <work_end/>
        <work_notes/>
        <work_notes_list/>
        <work_start/>
    </x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1>
</record_update>
]]></payload>
        <sys_class_name>sys_metadata_link</sys_class_name>
        <sys_created_by>admin</sys_created_by>
        <sys_created_on>2020-06-23 20:26:03</sys_created_on>
        <sys_id>941f3b06db251010280df36f29961920</sys_id>
        <sys_mod_count>0</sys_mod_count>
        <sys_name>IA-05</sys_name>
        <sys_package display_value="Rapid ATO" source="x_415531_rapid_ato">64898e36db501010280df36f29961934</sys_package>
        <sys_policy/>
        <sys_scope display_value="Rapid ATO">64898e36db501010280df36f29961934</sys_scope>
        <sys_update_name>sys_metadata_link_941f3b06db251010280df36f29961920</sys_update_name>
        <sys_updated_by>admin</sys_updated_by>
        <sys_updated_on>2020-06-23 20:26:03</sys_updated_on>
        <tablename>x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1</tablename>
    </sys_metadata_link>
</record_update>
