<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><record_update table="sys_metadata_link">
    <sys_metadata_link action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE">
        <directory>unload</directory>
        <documentkey>cd87f9fcdb211010280df36f29961913</documentkey>
        <payload><![CDATA[<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><record_update sys_domain="09ff3d105f231000b12e3572f2b4775d" table="x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1">
    <x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1 action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE">
        <active>true</active>
        <activity_due/>
        <additional_assignee_list/>
        <approval>not requested</approval>
        <approval_history/>
        <approval_set/>
        <ars_id display_value="ARS 3.1">43903e93dbcd1010280df36f299619aa</ars_id>
        <assessment_methods_and_objects>Examine: Contingency planning policy; </assessment_methods_and_objects>
        <assessment_objective>Determine if the organization has implemented all elements of this control as described in the control statements and implementation standard(s).</assessment_objective>
        <assigned_to/>
        <assignment_group/>
        <assurance/>
        <baseline>High; Moderate</baseline>
        <business_duration/>
        <business_service/>
        <calendar_duration/>
        <close_notes/>
        <closed_at/>
        <closed_by/>
        <cmdb_ci/>
        <comments/>
        <comments_and_work_notes/>
        <company/>
        <contact_type/>
        <contract/>
        <control_definition>The organization: a. Establishes an alternate processing site, including necessary agreements to permit the transfer and resumption of information system operation types defined by CMS for essential missions/business functions within an allowable outage time as specified by the system contingency plan or COOP for the business function(s) supported by the system when the primary processing capabilities are unavailable; b. Ensures that equipment and supplies required to transfer and resume operations are available at the alternate processing site or contracts are in place to support delivery to the site within the organization-defined time period for transfer/resumption; and c. Ensures that the alternate processing site provides information security safeguards equivalent to that of the primary site.</control_definition>
        <control_family display_value="Contingency Planning">c587b9fcdb211010280df36f299619f8</control_family>
        <control_name>Alternate Processing Site</control_name>
        <control_number>CP-07</control_number>
        <control_type>Mandatory</control_type>
        <correlation_display/>
        <correlation_id/>
        <delivery_plan/>
        <delivery_task/>
        <description/>
        <due_date/>
        <escalation>0</escalation>
        <expected_start/>
        <follow_up/>
        <group_id>CP-07</group_id>
        <group_list/>
        <high>true</high>
        <impact>3</impact>
        <implementation_standards>Systems defined as CSPs:&#13;
&#13;
High &amp; Moderate:&#13;
&#13;
CSP.1 - For CSPs, the organization defines a resumption time period consistent with the recovery time objectives and business impact analysis. The resum</implementation_standards>
        <knowledge>false</knowledge>
        <location/>
        <low>false</low>
        <made_sla>true</made_sla>
        <moderate>true</moderate>
        <number>ARSC0010964</number>
        <opened_at>2020-06-19 13:21:24</opened_at>
        <opened_by display_value="System Administrator">6816f79cc0a8016401c5a33be04be441</opened_by>
        <order/>
        <parent/>
        <priority>3</priority>
        <reassignment_count>0</reassignment_count>
        <reference_policy>FedRAMP Rev. 4 Baseline; FISCAM: AS-5, CP-2; HIPAA: 45 C.F.R. §164.308(a)(7)(ii)(B), 45 C.F.R. §164.310(a)(2)(i), 45 C.F.R. §164.308(7)(ii)(C); NIST SP: 800-34; PPD-21;</reference_policy>
        <rejection_goto/>
        <related_controls>CP-2, CP-6, CP-8, CP-9, CP-10, MA-6</related_controls>
        <service_offering/>
        <short_description/>
        <sla_due/>
        <standard>NIST-800</standard>
        <state>1</state>
        <supplemental_guidance>Alternate processing sites are sites that are geographically distinct from primary processing sites. An alternate processing site provides processing capability if the primary processing site is not available. Items covered by alternate processing site agreements include, for example, environmental conditions at alternate sites, access rules, physical and environmental protection requirements, and coordination for the transfer/assignment of personnel. Requirements are specifically allocated to alternate processing sites that reflect the requirements in contingency plans to maintain essential missions/business functions despite disruption, compromise, or failure in organizational information systems.Equipment and supplies required to resume operations within the CMS-defined period are either available at the alternate site or contracts are in place to support delivery to the site. Timeframes to resume information system operations are consistent with CMS recovery time objectives.&#13;
&#13;
Guidance for systems processing, storing, or transmitting PII (to include PHI):&#13;
&#13;
When an alternate processing site is used, administrative, physical and technical controls must be implemented to protect personally identifiable information (PII) in accordance with the privacy risks identified.&#13;
&#13;
Guidance for systems processing, storing, or transmitting PHI:&#13;
&#13;
When an alternate processing site is used, administrative, physical and technical controls must be implemented to protect PHI in accordance with the organization’s risk analysis.</supplemental_guidance>
        <sys_class_name>x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1</sys_class_name>
        <sys_created_by>admin</sys_created_by>
        <sys_created_on>2020-06-19 13:21:24</sys_created_on>
        <sys_domain>09ff3d105f231000b12e3572f2b4775d</sys_domain>
        <sys_domain_path>!!!/!!!/</sys_domain_path>
        <sys_id>cd87f9fcdb211010280df36f29961913</sys_id>
        <sys_mod_count>0</sys_mod_count>
        <sys_updated_by>admin</sys_updated_by>
        <sys_updated_on>2020-06-19 13:21:24</sys_updated_on>
        <task_for/>
        <time_worked/>
        <upon_approval>proceed</upon_approval>
        <upon_reject>cancel</upon_reject>
        <urgency>3</urgency>
        <user_input/>
        <variables/>
        <watch_list/>
        <wf_activity/>
        <work_end/>
        <work_notes/>
        <work_notes_list/>
        <work_start/>
    </x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1>
</record_update>
]]></payload>
        <sys_class_name>sys_metadata_link</sys_class_name>
        <sys_created_by>admin</sys_created_by>
        <sys_created_on>2020-06-23 20:26:33</sys_created_on>
        <sys_id>7b2f3f06db251010280df36f2996195b</sys_id>
        <sys_mod_count>0</sys_mod_count>
        <sys_name>CP-07</sys_name>
        <sys_package display_value="Rapid ATO" source="x_415531_rapid_ato">64898e36db501010280df36f29961934</sys_package>
        <sys_policy/>
        <sys_scope display_value="Rapid ATO">64898e36db501010280df36f29961934</sys_scope>
        <sys_update_name>sys_metadata_link_7b2f3f06db251010280df36f2996195b</sys_update_name>
        <sys_updated_by>admin</sys_updated_by>
        <sys_updated_on>2020-06-23 20:26:33</sys_updated_on>
        <tablename>x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1</tablename>
    </sys_metadata_link>
</record_update>
