<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><record_update table="sys_metadata_link">
    <sys_metadata_link action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE">
        <directory>unload</directory>
        <documentkey>3c87b9fcdb211010280df36f299619ad</documentkey>
        <payload><![CDATA[<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><record_update sys_domain="09ff3d105f231000b12e3572f2b4775d" table="x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1">
    <x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1 action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE">
        <active>true</active>
        <activity_due/>
        <additional_assignee_list/>
        <approval>not requested</approval>
        <approval_history/>
        <approval_set/>
        <ars_id display_value="ARS 3.1">43903e93dbcd1010280df36f299619aa</ars_id>
        <assessment_methods_and_objects>Examine: Security assessment and autho</assessment_methods_and_objects>
        <assessment_objective>Determine if the organization has implemented all elements of this control as described in the control statements and implementation standard(s).</assessment_objective>
        <assigned_to/>
        <assignment_group/>
        <assurance>Assurance</assurance>
        <baseline>High; Moderate; Low</baseline>
        <business_duration/>
        <business_service/>
        <calendar_duration/>
        <close_notes/>
        <closed_at/>
        <closed_by/>
        <cmdb_ci/>
        <comments/>
        <comments_and_work_notes/>
        <company/>
        <contact_type/>
        <contract/>
        <control_definition>The organization develops a continuous monitoring strategy and implements a continuous monitoring program that includes: a. Establishment of defined metrics (defined in the applicable system security plan) to be monitored based on the organization security goals and objectives and in accordance with the basic requirements set forth in NIST SP 800-137; b. Establishment of defined frequencies (defined in the applicable system security plan), but no less than once every 72 hours, for monitoring and defined frequencies (defined in the applicable system security plan), but no less than once every 72 hours, for assessments supporting such monitoring; c. Ongoing security control assessments in accordance with the organizational continuous monitoring strategy; d. Ongoing security status monitoring of organization-defined metrics in accordance with the organizational continuous monitoring strategy; e. Correlation and analysis of security-related information generated by assessments and monitoring; f. Response actions to address results of the analysis of security-related information; and g. Reporting the security status of the organization and the information system to defined personnel or roles (defined in the applicable system security plan) monthly.</control_definition>
        <control_family display_value="Security Assessment and Authorization">a887b9fcdb211010280df36f2996199b</control_family>
        <control_name>Continuous Monitoring</control_name>
        <control_number>CA-07</control_number>
        <control_type>Mandatory</control_type>
        <correlation_display/>
        <correlation_id/>
        <delivery_plan/>
        <delivery_task/>
        <description/>
        <due_date/>
        <escalation>0</escalation>
        <expected_start/>
        <follow_up/>
        <group_id>CA-07</group_id>
        <group_list/>
        <high>true</high>
        <impact>3</impact>
        <implementation_standards>High, Moderate &amp; Low:&#13;
&#13;
Std.1 - When subject to a legal investigation (e.g., of an insider threat), continuous monitoring records must be maintained until released by the investigating authority.Std.</implementation_standards>
        <knowledge>false</knowledge>
        <location/>
        <low>true</low>
        <made_sla>true</made_sla>
        <moderate>true</moderate>
        <number>ARSC0010904</number>
        <opened_at>2020-06-19 13:21:23</opened_at>
        <opened_by display_value="System Administrator">6816f79cc0a8016401c5a33be04be441</opened_by>
        <order/>
        <parent/>
        <priority>1</priority>
        <reassignment_count>0</reassignment_count>
        <reference_policy>Code: 5 U.S.C. §552a(e)(10); FedRAMP Rev. 4 Baseline; FISCAM: AS-1, SM-5; HHS: Policy for Monitoring Employee Use of HHS IT Resources; HIPAA: 45 C.F.R. §164.308(a)(1)(ii)(D), 45 C.F.R. §164.308(a)(8); 45 C.F.R. §164.308(a)(5)(ii)(C) HSPD 7: F(19); NIST SP: 800-37, 800-39, 800-115, 800-137; OMB Memo: M-11-33, M-14-03, M-15-01, M-16-04</reference_policy>
        <rejection_goto/>
        <related_controls>AR-4, CA-2, CA-5, CA-6, CM-3, CM-4, PM-6</related_controls>
        <service_offering/>
        <short_description/>
        <sla_due/>
        <standard>NIST-800</standard>
        <state>1</state>
        <supplemental_guidance>Continuous monitoring programs facilitate ongoing awareness of threats, vulnerabilities, and information security to support organizational risk management decisions. The terms “continuous” and “ongoing” imply that organizations assess/analyze security controls and information security-related risks at a frequency sufficient to support organizational risk-based decisions. The results of continuous monitoring programs generate appropriate risk response actions by organizations. Continuous monitoring programs also allow organizations to maintain the security authorizations of information systems and common controls over time in highly dynamic environments of operation with changing mission/business needs, threats, vulnerabilities, and technologies. Having access to security-related information on a continuing basis through reports/dashboards gives organizational officials the capability to make more effective and timely risk management decisions, including ongoing security authorization decisions. Automation supports more frequent updates to security authorization packages, hardware/software/firmware inventories, and other system information. Effectiveness is further enhanced when continuous monitoring outputs are formatted to provide information that is specific, measurable, actionable, relevant, and timely. Continuous monitoring activities are scaled in accordance with the security categories of information systems.&#13;
&#13;
Guidance for systems processing, storing, or transmitting PII (to include PHI):&#13;
&#13;
The state of security controls can directly correlate to privacy risk. Continuous monitoring supports the identification of issues that could result in unauthorized access to sensitive information such as PII, data quality issues, and other concerns, including privacy, that are supported by security controls.&#13;
&#13;
Guidance for systems processing, storing, or transmitting PHI:&#13;
&#13;
Consider using automated tools and mechanisms for system activity review. The effectiveness of continuous monitoring of various activities, for example, failed or successful log-ins, inappropriate file access, detecting and reporting on malicious code/viruses through network transmission, is enhanced using approved automated tools.</supplemental_guidance>
        <sys_class_name>x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1</sys_class_name>
        <sys_created_by>admin</sys_created_by>
        <sys_created_on>2020-06-19 13:21:23</sys_created_on>
        <sys_domain>09ff3d105f231000b12e3572f2b4775d</sys_domain>
        <sys_domain_path>!!!/!!!/</sys_domain_path>
        <sys_id>3c87b9fcdb211010280df36f299619ad</sys_id>
        <sys_mod_count>0</sys_mod_count>
        <sys_updated_by>admin</sys_updated_by>
        <sys_updated_on>2020-06-19 13:21:23</sys_updated_on>
        <task_for/>
        <time_worked/>
        <upon_approval>proceed</upon_approval>
        <upon_reject>cancel</upon_reject>
        <urgency>3</urgency>
        <user_input/>
        <variables/>
        <watch_list/>
        <wf_activity/>
        <work_end/>
        <work_notes/>
        <work_notes_list/>
        <work_start/>
    </x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1>
</record_update>
]]></payload>
        <sys_class_name>sys_metadata_link</sys_class_name>
        <sys_created_by>admin</sys_created_by>
        <sys_created_on>2020-06-23 20:26:08</sys_created_on>
        <sys_id>291f3b06db251010280df36f299619d8</sys_id>
        <sys_mod_count>0</sys_mod_count>
        <sys_name>CA-07</sys_name>
        <sys_package display_value="Rapid ATO" source="x_415531_rapid_ato">64898e36db501010280df36f29961934</sys_package>
        <sys_policy/>
        <sys_scope display_value="Rapid ATO">64898e36db501010280df36f29961934</sys_scope>
        <sys_update_name>sys_metadata_link_291f3b06db251010280df36f299619d8</sys_update_name>
        <sys_updated_by>admin</sys_updated_by>
        <sys_updated_on>2020-06-23 20:26:08</sys_updated_on>
        <tablename>x_415531_rapid_ato_ars_3_1</tablename>
    </sys_metadata_link>
</record_update>
